[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-12-03 20:44:14
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,20,1
Style: ED_CHINESE,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,20,1
Style: OP_CHINESE,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,20,1
Style: ED,ms gothic,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,0,0,30,128
Style: OP,ms gothic,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,0,0,30,128
Style: SP,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,110,110,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.88,0:00:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿林寮 #6\N爱上你真好 (后篇)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.95,0:00:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜， 可以帮我去买个东西吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.63,0:00:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,典马， 你可以陪她去吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.83,0:00:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怕她一个人不行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.67,0:00:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.97,0:00:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好典马就住在我们对面\N让阿姨能安心工作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.64,0:00:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,典马， 巳夜就麻烦你了\N要好好相处喔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.15,0:00:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯! 我最喜欢巳夜了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.95,0:00:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜， 要像典马一样\N当个好孩子喔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.62,0:00:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗? 巳夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.77,0:01:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.01,0:01:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那次之后， 不知她怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.88,0:01:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的提起勇气回家了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.33,0:01:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕， 钱包忘了拿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.08,0:01:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.38,0:01:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是...\N啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.39,0:01:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.19,0:01:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么? 五十岚来了?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.46,0:02:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯， 从宿舍的方向过来\N然后往车站跑去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.03,0:02:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川知道吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.67,0:02:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是回来通知他的\N不过他好像去买东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.47,0:02:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.14,0:02:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再增加阿莲的烦恼可能不太好\N还不是不要说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.64,0:02:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来， 五十岚那家伙\N为什么要来这里呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.32,0:02:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊， 不可能吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.22,0:02:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.42,0:02:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么， 我突然想到\N她会不会是来见莲川的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.93,0:02:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.29,0:02:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能\N而且她应该不会和小泉分手的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.90,0:02:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.61,0:02:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才为什么要逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.01,0:02:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来答谢当时他照顾我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.22,0:02:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明是来见他的， 为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.13,0:03:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆风与沙尘风暴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.47,0:03:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石块不断地掉落在泥泞中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.85,0:03:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从远方传来一道声音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.16,0:03:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家呼喊着你名字的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.50,0:03:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使赤脚奔跑很辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.17,0:03:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使希望毁灭了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.01,0:04:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拭去眼泪跑到这里来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.85,0:04:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有爱一定办得到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.70,0:04:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿越森林跨越万里之丘
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.54,0:04:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使海底也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.88,0:04:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川， 寒假你很闲对吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.45,0:04:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.22,0:04:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好， 就这样说定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.46,0:04:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.26,0:04:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家寺庙要大扫除\N我妈说会给你一些零用钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.70,0:04:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把它当作是打工吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.80,0:04:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.74,0:04:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.34,0:05:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带帮手来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.78,0:05:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊... 欢迎， 你是莲川同学吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.01,0:05:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊... 是， 您好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.91,0:05:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么那么没精神呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.25,0:05:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提起精神来， 提起精神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.09,0:05:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们家没有分什么外不外人的\N好好的干喔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.26,0:05:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿正
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.33,0:05:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊， 欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.10,0:05:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我弟弟正十\N我都叫他阿正
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.37,0:05:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是莲川
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.90,0:05:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂! 手脚不快点\N天就要黑了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.10,0:05:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这扇纸门弄破也没关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.97,0:05:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.04,0:05:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.05,0:05:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你每年都要搞这个\N才会高兴是吗， 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.06,0:05:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在学校或宿舍会不会很轻浮?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.03,0:05:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流学长吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.50,0:05:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为进了不适合他的绿都学园
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.96,0:05:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说会不会只有他一个人爱搞怪\N感觉很轻浮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.30,0:05:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很担心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.60,0:06:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事， 大家都像他那样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.94,0:06:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.71,0:06:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃午饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.61,0:06:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是帮了我们大忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.31,0:06:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今年爸爸还不能放假
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.08,0:06:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?你爸爸不是和尚吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.02,0:06:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是佛教学校的老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.85,0:06:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么寺庙呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.79,0:06:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流会继承的， 对吧\N因为他是长子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.73,0:06:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼!每个人都推来推去的\N随便你们好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.87,0:06:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间寺庙\N我会照料到我200岁的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.40,0:06:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦! 打扫， 打扫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.61,0:06:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长， 你最后还是得当和尚吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.65,0:06:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.31,0:06:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿正说的话别放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.12,0:06:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是希望光流能留在家里而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.66,0:06:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好像不太喜欢光流去住宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.46,0:07:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是小孩子\N不知道还要寂寞到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.70,0:07:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经是那个年龄了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.67,0:07:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你想做什么就去做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.97,0:07:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在意阿正和我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.47,0:07:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去做你想做的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.01,0:07:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.05,0:07:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15年前这个道路拓宽\N寺庙的院子变小了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.22,0:07:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一带有一个门
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.29,0:07:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参拜用的道路像这样延伸着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.69,0:07:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那棵树在那一边
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.06,0:07:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.73,0:07:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说就被丢在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.00,0:07:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.97,0:07:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 咦? 我没有跟你讲过吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.60,0:07:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不， 我知道\N从阿忍学长那里得知的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.01,0:07:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于自己的事你全都知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.38,0:07:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩子的时候常常听人说的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.55,0:07:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始吗? 都没瞒着你吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.18,0:07:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算想瞒也瞒不了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.02,0:07:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近的人大家都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.25,0:08:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在一个4月的温暖日子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.92,0:08:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被放在连翘花的下面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.93,0:08:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的周围散落着很多花瓣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.76,0:08:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睡得很甜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.37,0:08:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很庆幸从小就被告知这些
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.74,0:08:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不介意吗? 亲生父母的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.74,0:08:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,介意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.67,0:08:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道为什么把我丢在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.11,0:08:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.98,0:08:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和阿正一起来到这个家\N你们两个我都很喜欢喔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.65,0:08:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家人的感情表现很明显\N所以我不能继续变坏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.93,0:08:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么学长为什么要住在宿舍?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.80,0:08:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望早点离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.90,0:08:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在先让心情调适过来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.50,0:08:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.17,0:08:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你原来一直都是这么想的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.94,0:08:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿正
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.94,0:08:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流和我是家人的证明\N就只剩下你留家里这一点而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.81,0:09:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那么想当外人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.85,0:09:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是想当\N事实上我就是外人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.69,0:09:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你!笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.03,0:09:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长， 你讲得太过份了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.96,0:09:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实就是事实\N想隐瞒也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.40,0:09:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.44,0:09:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.77,0:09:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外人终究还是比不上兄弟吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.45,0:09:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你提
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.68,0:09:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了， 才这样而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.22,0:09:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的， 你最近跟我\N分得那么清楚做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.09,0:09:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说\N自己的东西我自己会提
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.19,0:09:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办? 怎么办才好?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.03,0:09:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于刚刚的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.80,0:09:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚的?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.23,0:09:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为血缘关系不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最重要的是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.14,0:09:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最重要的是爱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.58,0:10:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在想那件事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.11,0:10:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.98,0:10:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川， 这样说或许很失礼\N你追不到五十岚的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.95,0:10:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对手太强了， 那个叫小泉的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.96,0:10:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁还没陷进去之前， 死了心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.72,0:10:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.79,0:10:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是若交给那家伙的话\N她会幸福吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.70,0:10:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得他们两人之间\N欠缺了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.50,0:10:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚会一直很担心\N会被那个人讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.55,0:10:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊， 池田学长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.72,0:10:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.15,0:10:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这里遇见她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.63,0:10:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那个表情我见过\N就是快要哭出来的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.83,0:11:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔... 五十岚的妈妈回来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.37,0:11:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯， 听说暂时会留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.91,0:11:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊， 巳夜\N上次的事你谢过人家了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.44,0:11:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 啊... 那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.84,0:11:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.74,0:11:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好谢谢人家才行\N去吧， 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.58,0:11:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时真的很对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.99,0:11:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.99,0:11:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的宿舍长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.42,0:11:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要道谢就向他说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.52,0:11:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔， 这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.77,0:11:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.27,0:11:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么再见啰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.74,0:11:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.34,0:11:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新年快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.02,0:11:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车钱我帮你出吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.92,0:11:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.36,0:12:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 喂...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.13,0:12:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样， 面纸拿去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.87,0:12:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长， 我该怎么做才好?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.64,0:12:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么做啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.24,0:12:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得头脑充满了血\N好难过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.11,0:12:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在好不甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.28,0:12:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这种事我不想插手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.06,0:12:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样做真的太鸡婆了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.20,0:12:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀， 小也脸红红的\N是不是发烧了?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.11,0:12:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然， 会是感冒吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.91,0:12:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去躺着才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.48,0:12:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿弘， 阿弘
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.55,0:12:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.45,0:12:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在小也的牛仔裤口袋里找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.42,0:13:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔... 那家伙...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.32,0:13:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦! 背面， 背面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.16,0:13:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.70,0:13:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了， 因为五十岚住在那一带
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.70,0:13:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以会在莺谷碰到也不意外
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.70,0:13:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在一定正和那家伙\N去新年参拜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.07,0:13:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.28,0:13:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么"有爱就会变强"\N都是骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.01,0:13:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一也， 差不多要吃午饭了\N你吃得下吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.08,0:13:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.22,0:13:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.59,0:13:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有事想问你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.35,0:13:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一也竟然会找我商量事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.42,0:13:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等待这天的再度来临\N不知道等了多久
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.53,0:13:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.70,0:13:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是举例而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.70,0:13:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果哥哥与小菫认识时\N小菫已经有喜欢的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.84,0:13:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥会怎么做?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.67,0:13:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊， 你不觉得举这种例子\N一点意义都没有吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.71,0:13:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说例如嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.88,0:14:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会怎么做是什么意思?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.18,0:14:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说， 哥哥喜欢小菫\N但是小菫却喜欢其他的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.92,0:14:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.59,0:14:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就放弃吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.89,0:14:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的话， 不管条件如何\N我的答案都一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.26,0:14:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管那两人交往了多久\N我都不会退让的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.77,0:14:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是自己的弟弟\N我也不会心软
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.91,0:14:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你想太多这种无聊的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.61,0:14:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这不只是我一个人的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.38,0:14:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许会伤到她或是那个男的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.68,0:14:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别去管那个男的\N笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.02,0:14:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是在担心\N自己会不会变成坏人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.09,0:14:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.33,0:14:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我只是怕自己受伤罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.50,0:14:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答案明明就只有那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.50,0:14:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便再告诉你一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.14,0:14:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.07,0:14:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你被断然拒绝\N那么就只有你会受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.14,0:15:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为罪恶会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.44,0:15:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过就算没消失\N也不一定是罪恶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.95,0:15:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到最后还是得由她来决定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.28,0:15:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她是五十岚啰
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.65,0:15:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你... 你怎么会知道?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.03,0:15:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(五十岚)
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.59,0:15:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个鸡婆的人写的字\N我常看过嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.56,0:15:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以他的作风来说\N这算是很低调的同意讯息
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.64,0:15:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之要向五十岚表白我的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.21,0:15:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切得先从这里开始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.94,0:15:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.63,0:15:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂! 这里是五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.89,0:15:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起， 麻烦找巳夜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.60,0:15:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.23,0:16:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚! 我是莲川\N我有话想跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.50,0:16:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.57,0:16:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.51,0:16:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜， 谁打来的? 朋友吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.28,0:16:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是! 他打错了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.18,0:16:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.58,0:16:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜， 要不要吃典马妈妈\N做的年菜? 很好吃喔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.19,0:16:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.50,0:16:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?小也被拒绝了是吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.94,0:16:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怜喔\N不过俗话说"初恋注定要失败"
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.17,0:16:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要灰心喔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.51,0:16:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一也
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.05,0:16:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说错什么了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.52,0:16:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时的感冒没治好\N从过年开始就一直不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.09,0:16:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今都还躺在病床上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.19,0:17:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因爱情而病至发烧的人\N倒是很少见
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.56,0:17:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还一直坚持着\N在明天寒假结束前要回宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.70,0:17:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这个问题\N看来连光流也帮不了他了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.84,0:17:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你有办法帮他吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.34,0:17:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.58,0:17:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能会去帮他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.18,0:17:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过说的也是\N阿莲真是个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.91,0:17:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得可真轻松啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.42,0:17:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就是啊\N大姊的事我还能理解喔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.72,0:17:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是五十岚真有那么好吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.15,0:17:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个诚实的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.59,0:17:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这次和大姊的事\N有一点完全不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.79,0:17:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.46,0:17:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是还没分出胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.87,0:17:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来\N五十岚那家伙到底在想什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.94,0:17:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然不说话就挂掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.41,0:17:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川真的有希望吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.58,0:17:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会早就被讨厌了?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.38,0:17:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得应该有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.28,0:17:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好不容易取回了\N身为哥哥的信赖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.58,0:17:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你做了鸡婆的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.55,0:18:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了鸡婆事的人是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.12,0:18:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正像你这种玩弄女人的人\N想要了解一也的纯情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.19,0:18:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本就是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.69,0:18:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是神经错乱的时候吧\N大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.70,0:18:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.47,0:18:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要帮他想个法子才行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.43,0:18:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔， 好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.97,0:18:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨， 过得好吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.07,0:18:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂， 你知道吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.94,0:18:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说莲川终于对之前那个\N不良少女表白了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.11,0:18:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 原来他是认真的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.54,0:18:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是那个女的\N不是已经有男人了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.15,0:18:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊\N在元旦那天就被拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.98,0:18:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真酷! 不愧是莲川学长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.19,0:18:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然明知道会这样子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.96,0:18:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是不说话就挂掉\N这也太过分了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.76,0:18:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.96,0:18:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像今天会回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.47,0:18:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.74,0:18:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.90,0:18:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.34,0:18:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔， 什么事?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.44,0:18:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请告诉我五十岚的住址
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.04,0:18:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲， 你要写情书吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.55,0:19:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来还有这个方法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.88,0:19:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等... 等等\N难不成你想直接找她讲吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.39,0:19:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打了好几次的电话\N都没有人接
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.02,0:19:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有其他方法了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.02,0:19:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你不是已经被拒绝了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.06,0:19:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.76,0:19:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都还没说\N但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.00,0:19:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.73,0:19:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么"对不起"嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.34,0:19:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.87,0:19:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算结果是一样\N我也不能就此放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.91,0:19:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我向她告白\N或是她明确拒绝我之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.31,0:19:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不算结束
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.22,0:19:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚你的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.42,0:19:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是突然跑进女生家里\N是很没有常识的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.15,0:19:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那该怎么办?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.79,0:19:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是有学校吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.36,0:19:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊... 学校的话\N她每天都会经过嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.26,0:19:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此， 好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.36,0:19:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川， 我们被你感动了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.87,0:19:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.10,0:19:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们支持你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.44,0:19:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.40,0:19:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬着头皮冲吧\N这就是青春
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.97,0:20:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊! 冲啊! 往前冲!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.22,0:20:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是那个青梅竹马\N他是个什么样的人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.45,0:20:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫作小泉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.46,0:20:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是很清楚\N他住在五十岚家的对面
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.66,0:20:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚的妈妈\N因为工作常常不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.86,0:20:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以五十岚小时候\N好像常常被寄放在小泉家里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.20,0:20:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是家人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.87,0:20:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.50,0:20:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小学的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.24,0:20:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要五十岚出了什么事\N小泉一定会帮她出头
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.04,0:20:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚也一直\N跟着小泉后面走着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.45,0:20:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上中学后五十岚会突然变坏\N也是因为小泉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.22,0:20:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么， 阿莲的希望不就...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.35,0:20:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定没了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.02,0:20:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如今的莲川\N就算眼前是一整片的地雷区
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.06,0:20:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会向前冲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.76,0:20:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能随他去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.93,0:20:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒好了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.63,0:20:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.40,0:21:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么， 从今天开始...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.97,0:21:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的， 我要出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.44,0:21:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.50,0:21:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要被拒绝了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.38,0:21:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?你还在织毛衣啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.55,0:21:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为毛线老是松掉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.09,0:21:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.02,0:21:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请假吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.86,0:21:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也不在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.40,0:21:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.74,0:21:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还想继续吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.44,0:21:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天到女校报到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.81,0:21:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方不是有男朋友了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.27,0:21:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我知道他很有毅力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.81,0:21:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样? 五十岚家的电话?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.22,0:21:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人接， 不管何时打都没人接
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.55,0:21:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许该想想别的方法了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.82,0:21:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能让阿莲\N老是翘第6节课啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.43,0:22:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不是一起在翘课
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.60,0:22:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长你才是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.80,0:22:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊... 又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.67,0:22:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂， 喂， 你在做什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.73,0:22:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊， 学长， 危机! 危机!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.77,0:22:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像每天都在这里出现\N你找我们学校有事吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.84,0:22:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在等朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.08,0:22:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友? 谁啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.35,0:22:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.68,0:22:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好危险
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.45,0:22:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂， 喂， 他说的五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.49,0:22:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们班上的五十岚吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.86,0:22:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她请假喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.52,0:22:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手骨折住院了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.59,0:22:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骨... 骨折? 为什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.36,0:22:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯... 好像是寒假去滑雪时\N跌倒受伤的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.53,0:22:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪间医院?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.24,0:22:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦... 我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.44,0:22:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道是哪家医院了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.01,0:22:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.21,0:22:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是医院就可以\N以探病为由大大方方去找她了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.45,0:22:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天医院休息， 后天再去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.85,0:22:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.08,0:23:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚巳夜?今天早上出院了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.86,0:23:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全忘记了\N莲川你的那个超级倒楣运
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.23,0:23:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比预料中还提早出院\N真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.80,0:23:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么， 阿姨你今天请假啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.64,0:23:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啊! 这种时候\N我一定要在巳夜身旁陪她才行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.28,0:23:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是报应\N他一定很生气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.82,0:23:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是， 如果现在跟他说话的话\N我会...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.35,0:23:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过阿姨真的觉得\N幸好有典马在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.42,0:23:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托你的福\N阿姨可以安心去上班
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.76,0:23:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜也变成很乖的孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.86,0:23:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想说倒不如\N你来当我家的孩子好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.57,0:23:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系， 阿姨\N我会好好照顾巳夜的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.17,0:23:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是靠得住， 对不对? 巳夜
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.01,0:23:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊， 电话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.15,0:23:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.52,0:24:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?恶作剧的电话吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.40,0:24:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿忍学长， 请给我便条纸
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.44,0:24:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇... 他已经豁出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.78,0:24:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.11,0:24:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到你受伤住院时， 我吓了 一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.31,0:24:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在伤势怎样了呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.45,0:24:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话想当面对你说\N下星期一我会去你学校等你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.29,0:24:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在校门口附近等我\N请你一定要等我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.37,0:24:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚同学
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.27,0:25:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近有个男生时常来等你\N今天又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.44,0:25:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么关系呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.98,0:25:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚同学
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.82,0:25:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.93,0:25:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她果然还是没来
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.27,0:25:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里的话\N是会被学校老师骂的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.14,0:25:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间学校规定男女交往\N是需要父母同意的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.11,0:25:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会在这里?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.58,0:25:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来接巳夜的， 所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.19,0:25:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄这种东西来也没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.59,0:25:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个... 五十岚没有看过吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.49,0:25:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会让她看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.66,0:25:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果让她妈妈看见了\N你不觉得会造成巳夜的困扰吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.67,0:26:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜的妈妈是站在我这边的\N今后我们两家也得持续来往
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.84,0:26:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这种鸡婆的事\N只会让巳夜的立场难堪而已
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.24,0:26:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我喜欢五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.68,0:26:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.76,0:26:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家吧! 巳夜
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.39,0:26:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.20,0:26:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要躲我? 五十岚
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.84,0:26:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.71,0:26:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在躲避他吗? 不是\N那我是在躲什么呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.08,0:26:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再喜欢他就好了\N现在这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.32,0:26:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想跟妈妈或是典马争吵
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.99,0:26:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以把他忘了\N不要再见面就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.26,0:27:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.86,0:27:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真没用， 只会哭， 老是在逃避
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.40,0:27:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明知道一直逃避\N是解决不了问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.14,0:27:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要在意， 巳夜
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.14,0:27:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我最了解你了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.44,0:27:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我都会保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.91,0:27:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳夜只要维持这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.38,0:27:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我喜欢他
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.66,0:27:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊... 然后呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.55,0:27:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂， 到底怎么样了? 小瞬
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.65,0:28:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.12,0:28:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赌会成功一千元耶
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.46,0:28:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了! 安静点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.39,0:28:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场雨...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.83,0:28:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经分出胜负了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.90,0:28:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天究竟发生了什么事?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.47,0:28:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N再见
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.83,0:28:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校门外有一个女生耶
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.77,0:28:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.71,0:28:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲， 雨伞
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.84,0:28:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是个普通的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.18,0:29:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么地称赞了他
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.85,0:29:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的胸口扑通扑通地跳着
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.69,0:29:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他发现就不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.37,0:29:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想被他看到眼泪
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.04,0:29:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因而逃走的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.71,0:29:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能再多说一句话
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.22,0:29:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切就能改变
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.36,0:29:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天还有之前电话的事\N对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.36,0:29:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.36,0:29:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我被老师骂了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.67,0:29:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.20,0:29:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊... 对不起\N我没想到你们的校规
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.60,0:29:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也和典马吵架了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.97,0:29:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.94,0:30:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈从昨晚开始都不跟我说话
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.44,0:30:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.21,0:30:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我还是想见你
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.38,0:30:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且想让自己变得更成熟一点
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.12,0:30:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.35,0:30:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.99,0:30:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会陪着你
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.42,0:30:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你真好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.60,0:30:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时 一直都是 永远都是
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.61,0:30:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要看着你的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.48,0:31:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不轮给任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.15,0:31:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此的死要面子
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.66,0:31:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明知道逞强是最差劲的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.00,0:31:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为发生太多悲伤的事
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.35,0:31:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记了温柔的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.85,0:31:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法正视你
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.16,0:32:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躺在草地上
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.20,0:32:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉默不语
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.71,0:32:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人一起感受着微风
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.88,0:32:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你真好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.89,0:32:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你真好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.23,0:32:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时 一直都是永远都是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.91,0:32:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会陪你走下去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.58,0:33:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你真好
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.76,0:33:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你真好
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.93,0:33:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时 一直都是永远都是
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.11,0:33:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要看着你的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.17,0:34:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上你真好


