[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-12-03 20:44:14
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,20,1
Style: ED_CHINESE,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,20,1
Style: OP_CHINESE,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,20,1
Style: ED,ms gothic,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,0,0,30,128
Style: OP,ms gothic,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,0,0,30,128
Style: SP,simhei,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,110,110,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.51,0:00:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于来到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.85,0:00:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？小也要住宿舍吗？为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.12,0:00:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来以为终于可以一起生活了为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.29,0:00:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫莲川一也
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.16,0:00:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今天开始要住在绿都学园的宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.76,0:00:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唯一的亲人哥哥一弘
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.76,0:00:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年春天刚结婚所以我的家是一个新婚家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.60,0:00:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了反正小也就是讨厌我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.41,0:00:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走吧！宿舍也好，哪里都行！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.04,0:00:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情况下真有人可以住得下去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.15,0:00:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与如今是别人老婆的初恋情人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.15,0:00:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在同一个屋檐下…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.89,0:00:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你入学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.79,0:01:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天起你就是本学园的学生了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.53,0:01:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外也恭喜你出院
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.69,0:01:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是一场灾难不过真高兴你能痊愈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.80,0:01:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的关心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.23,0:01:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过，辛苦的现在才要开始喔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.67,0:01:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中生活的头一个月你都缺席这对你相当的不利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.88,0:01:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川同学你一定要弥补这段空缺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.55,0:01:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.28,0:01:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.95,0:01:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有够惨的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.39,0:01:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来参观学校的那天在校门□差点被车撞到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.36,0:01:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试那天因为大风雪电车停开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.76,0:01:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合格通知单因为邮局的作业疏失而延误收到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.63,0:01:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更糟糕的是入学前一天住院
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.50,0:01:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…可是我已经无家可归了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.34,0:01:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不能认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.34,0:01:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.96,0:02:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来介绍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.79,0:02:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是学生会的会长手冢忍同学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.26,0:02:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是宿舍长池田光流同学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.16,0:02:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.06,0:02:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.97,0:02:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着由我带你去参观宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.34,0:02:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两位都是宿舍的学长可以把他们当成自己的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.64,0:02:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事就找他们商量吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.77,0:02:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.61,0:02:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入哥哥以前念过的绿都学园是我的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.22,0:02:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸妈死后靠自己一个人把我养大成人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.89,0:02:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是住家附近无人不知的模范生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.09,0:02:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他却粉碎了我的理想…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.73,0:02:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.59,0:02:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.30,0:02:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.73,0:02:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你一开学就住院真是倒楣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.83,0:02:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是生了什么病吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.94,0:02:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，也可以这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.00,0:02:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是喔！不过恢复健康就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.07,0:03:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位叫池田的人和高中时期的一弘有点像
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.65,0:03:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是你以后的家绿林寮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.25,0:03:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都叫这里为Green Wood
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.19,0:03:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Green Wood?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.69,0:03:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为绿林寮比较不好念
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.32,0:03:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很期待你的到来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.50,0:03:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿舍里禁止招募社员的活动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.97,0:03:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不会有人来找你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.04,0:03:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里虽然附属于学校但却算是独立的设施
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.14,0:03:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藉此保障宿舍里的个人生活
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.58,0:03:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎！莲川一也同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.45,0:03:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在正透过贩售圣经让大家了解上帝的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.46,0:03:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个你就不用太在意了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.83,0:03:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是你的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.59,0:03:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！室友来啰！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:03:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对喔，两个人住一间喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.87,0:04:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？莲川同学
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.91,0:04:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才里面有女生…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.31,0:04:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔，那就是你的室友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.18,0:04:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如月瞬同学
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.18,0:04:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓我一跳 我还以为真的是女生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.59,0:04:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是女生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.72,0:04:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.56,0:04:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是一年级请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.19,0:04:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会吓一跳也是正常的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.03,0:04:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今后你们要同住一室所以要先让你知道清楚才行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.83,0:04:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实在她对我们坦白前我们都没察觉到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.80,0:04:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都认为只是跟别人不一样而已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.91,0:04:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子的户籍和其他记录上都是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.64,0:04:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过她是个真正的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.81,0:04:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说是因为某种原因
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.08,0:04:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以一出生就被当成男生来看待
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.62,0:04:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于是什么原因现在不方便跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.42,0:04:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之她是名叫如月瞬的男学生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.32,0:04:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须以男生的身份从这个学校毕业
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.03,0:05:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.03,0:05:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啰，莲川同学希望你也能帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.40,0:05:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事是除了我们四个人之外绝不能让其他人知道的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.40,0:05:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点辛苦但是为了她
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.97,0:05:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能多多帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.08,0:05:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们先走啰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.14,0:05:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地休息趁早习，陨这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.45,0:05:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.02,0:05:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我怎么和一个假装男人的女生在此一起生活三年啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.82,0:05:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如月同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.66,0:05:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我小瞬就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.09,0:05:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样子真的好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.53,0:05:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯！我一直都念男校所以习惯了而且我相信莲川同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.27,0:05:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别随便相信别人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.50,0:05:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川同学，刚刚忘记说了这栋建筑物很老旧了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.58,0:05:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墙壁很薄我们的房间就在隔壁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.14,0:05:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一我们要是听到她的惨叫声
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.95,0:05:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时我们可是不会轻易放过你的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.36,0:06:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起，你很困扰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.69,0:06:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我很清楚的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.56,0:06:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你住院的这段期间老实说我过得很轻松
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.96,0:06:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我真的给你带来困扰你去跟舍监的大婶说没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.87,0:06:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不会…哪有什么困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.67,0:06:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.28,0:06:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,210室的莲川同学有你的行李
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.05,0:06:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，莲川同学的行李好像来了我也去帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.76,0:06:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.17,0:06:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样根本什么都没变嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.68,0:06:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲…阿莲…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.65,0:07:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等一下喔我现在正在换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.62,0:07:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川同学，我可以叫你阿莲吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.46,0:07:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.26,0:07:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔，莲川，早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.06,0:07:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，早安
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.87,0:07:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得好吗？今天你要开始上课了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.27,0:07:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.34,0:07:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,课程可能会很吃力如果你愿意，我们随时都会帮你的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.71,0:07:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.44,0:07:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不同班真是可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.05,0:07:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么，今天就上到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全听不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.75,0:07:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川听说你和那个如月同寝室啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.42,0:07:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识那家伙啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.86,0:07:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊，可是一个有名人物呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.83,0:07:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油喔！莲川
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.50,0:07:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿林寮本来就是一群怪人的巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.50,0:07:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过，如月如果真的是女的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.97,0:07:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我会很高兴地搬进去他的房间住
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.21,0:07:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你来跟我换啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.67,0:08:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过就算是男校但是女生实在也太少了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.84,0:08:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊！而且只有我们的学校连校医都是男生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.71,0:08:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.98,0:08:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧？你也这么想吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.98,0:08:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当初是不是打算进女校啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.55,0:08:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有传闻说他是男同性恋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.53,0:08:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不好意思这点小伤也来…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.80,0:08:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.10,0:08:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保健室就是为你们而开的啊随时欢迎你来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.13,0:08:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太麻烦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.41,0:08:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一也
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.18,0:08:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把亲哥哥当成什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.78,0:08:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋态
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.29,0:08:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得有你这种亲哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.86,0:08:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.56,0:08:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有什么让你不高兴呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.76,0:08:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的亲哥哥是更有男人味而且神采奕奕的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会沦落到得在男校悲惨地渡过余生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.67,0:09:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.67,0:09:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了，我话说在前面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.78,0:09:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在学校你我彼此不认识也不是兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.88,0:09:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.71,0:09:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.45,0:09:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要把小堇弄哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.72,0:09:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会这么做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.16,0:09:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对自己最爱的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.43,0:09:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最爱的妻子耶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.23,0:09:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是值得捉弄的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.74,0:09:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要像一弘那样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.37,0:09:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要活得像样一点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.61,0:09:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.55,0:09:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定得装成男生对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.39,0:09:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把自己弄得更像男生一点应该比较好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.19,0:09:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是头发…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.66,0:10:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来，反而会更容易被发现
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.70,0:10:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如像这样豁出去待在男校大家只会觉得是个怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.43,0:10:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不会感到奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.37,0:10:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.57,0:10:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果阿莲要我剪的话我就剪喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.77,0:10:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不，我不是这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.31,0:10:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲好可爱喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.68,0:10:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了，有件事想麻烦你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.78,0:10:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.78,0:10:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.19,0:10:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.36,0:10:35.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川同学是个正直的人真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.93,0:10:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以放心把如月交给你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.37,0:10:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,功课上有什么不懂的可以来问我们喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.14,0:10:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了，明天开始我帮你看一下好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.61,0:10:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.18,0:10:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不能再这样下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.28,0:10:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小瞬会让我分心根本无法看书
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.35,0:10:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要想个办法才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.16,0:11:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…今天要去问学长功课吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.99,0:11:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.59,0:11:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.13,0:11:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有问题要问我先走啰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.68,0:11:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.08,0:11:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.39,0:11:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.95,0:11:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是什么？咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.86,0:11:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再让我看一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.53,0:11:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色狼！不要啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.46,0:11:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰峻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.96,0:11:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.50,0:11:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都是光流学长和忍学长要我这样做的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.10,0:11:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.57,0:11:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流学长？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.44,0:11:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他终于发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.47,0:11:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第几天了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.27,0:11:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三天的下午
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.68,0:11:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶，输了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.18,0:11:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要再慢一天就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.25,0:12:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小瞬这个笨蛋一下子就露出马脚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.95,0:12:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌今天的人是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.48,0:12:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，终于被发现了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.29,0:12:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三天的下午
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.69,0:12:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔，赔率是1赔18真是意想不到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.32,0:12:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来有很多人要赔钱了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.46,0:12:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样很好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.36,0:12:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨，莲川，我们正在等你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.63,0:12:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一开学就长期旷课的笨蛋听说终于要来上课了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.67,0:12:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就觉得要办个盛大的欢迎会才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.54,0:12:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏你被骗了三天让我们赚了不少欢迎会的费用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.08,0:12:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近期我们将会隆重举办
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.45,0:12:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.69,0:12:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他揍了光流…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.42,0:12:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.49,0:12:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就说过了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.79,0:12:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是经不起玩笑的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.23,0:12:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打得真好，我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.81,0:13:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么连这个问题都不会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.07,0:13:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要随便打人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.51,0:13:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是自愿要来请教学长的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.75,0:13:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔…这种话最好还是留到期末考完再说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.72,0:13:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的期中考能过关不知道是谁的功劳喔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.82,0:13:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流，你对他要再温柔点才行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.43,0:13:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可是一个因为考试而得到胄溃疡的纤细少年啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.57,0:13:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢我不是因为考试而胄溃疡的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.81,0:13:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入绿林寮已经两个多月了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.65,0:13:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿舍里住着许多在绿都学园中特别会引人注目的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.68,0:13:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都像女生的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.72,0:13:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古泽学长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.36,0:13:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨，阿莲，瞬弟一切还好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.79,0:13:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在房间内和机车一起生活的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.77,0:14:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉，如果宿舍里有地方停就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.04,0:14:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有某宗教的基层组织
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.24,0:14:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有人把房间当成电玩中心赚了不少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.38,0:14:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之，只要再忍一忍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.12,0:14:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等期末考一结束就可以一个人安静的过暑假
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.85,0:14:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.12,0:14:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！别那么明显的摆出那种厌恶的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.66,0:14:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你偶尔也去别的地方坐坐如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.29,0:14:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要坐哪里是我的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.43,0:14:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要坐哪里的确是你的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.70,0:14:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流学长可真会吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.94,0:14:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为要耗费非常大的能源来维持这张脸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.81,0:14:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.88,0:14:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了，莲川好像有看到你的留宿申请
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.18,0:14:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你暑假不回去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.85,0:14:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，因为有一些事…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.88,0:14:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的很用功喔，莲川我原本还以为你完了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.96,0:14:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那保重了喔我会买土产回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.83,0:15:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了期待已久的宁静生活终于来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.07,0:15:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来是这么以为…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.70,0:15:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们还留在这里呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.64,0:15:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛…有很多原因
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.21,0:15:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感到可惜的是我们才对吧？阿忍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.11,0:15:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本以为终于能有两人独处的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.55,0:15:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.88,0:15:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川用白眼在看我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.99,0:15:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是开不起玩笑的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.62,0:15:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提出申请的有19人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.72,0:15:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没有擅自留下的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.73,0:15:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有暑假期间的打扫、门禁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.43,0:15:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一律跟往常一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.07,0:15:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这么多人在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.94,0:15:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过，平常有200人的地方现在只剩19人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.01,0:15:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确是安静多了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.01,0:15:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小堇…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.65,0:15:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看来很闲嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.18,0:15:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.35,0:15:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去洗个澡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.79,0:16:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要反正你们一定有什么诡计…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.56,0:16:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手术的伤□是这里吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.13,0:16:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川，为什么不回家呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.53,0:16:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为哥哥结婚了我不想当电灯泡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.50,0:16:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？你这个大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.84,0:16:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是太浪费机会了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.37,0:16:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们不一样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.18,0:16:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成是那个吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.35,0:16:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上哥哥老婆的弟弟是吗？这种事常常听说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.88,0:16:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们又是为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.45,0:16:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流学长你家到底在哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.29,0:16:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的家在莺谷旁边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.82,0:16:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？学长是东京人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.16,0:16:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家住那么近为什么还要住宿舍呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.13,0:16:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道周围的人因为你而有多困扰吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.20,0:16:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你蛮敢讲的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.41,0:17:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.81,0:17:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子啊，那么拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.06,0:17:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,210室的莲川同学
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.33,0:17:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你姊姊来看你了请立刻到会客厅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.20,0:17:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.67,0:17:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔，莲川你在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.74,0:17:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小堇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.81,0:17:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小也
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.65,0:17:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种大热天…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.65,0:17:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真让人担心都暑假了为什么不回家呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.89,0:17:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用顾虑我因为小也你是我的弟弟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.43,0:17:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了，真的不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.20,0:18:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小也果然反对我们的结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.08,0:18:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本就是相依为命的兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.41,0:18:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他大概是觉得阿弘被我抢走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.51,0:18:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然她就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.25,0:18:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胄溃疡的原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.46,0:18:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋，我在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.69,0:18:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样小童会起疑的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.29,0:18:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，糟了，学长他们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.53,0:18:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会对小堇乱说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.77,0:18:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小堇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.04,0:18:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.40,0:18:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.14,0:18:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说看到你就好了之后的事就拜托我们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.24,0:18:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…美人走掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.48,0:18:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问学长你跟小堇怎么说的？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.82,0:18:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔我说你暑假期间如果不留校补修
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.12,0:18:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有可能被留级
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.65,0:18:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说你从昨晚开始就拉肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.56,0:18:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有意见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.89,0:18:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢…谢谢学长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.16,0:18:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.90,0:18:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起，小堇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.87,0:19:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我得早点忘记小堇才行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.40,0:19:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我怎样都不能回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.74,0:19:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一天小瞬也差不多要回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.94,0:19:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川，你的功课呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.68,0:19:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做完了，全部自己做了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.42,0:19:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要再欠你人情了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.12,0:19:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最近的脾气很瞥扭耶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.89,0:19:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为是谁害的啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.82,0:19:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，来了，小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.30,0:19:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那样好像每隔一阵子就会流行一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.33,0:19:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面中学的女学生看我们是男校所以跟我们闹着玩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.74,0:19:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.01,0:19:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长，阿莲，我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.85,0:19:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样子，她是一个大美人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.55,0:19:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？莲川的姊姊啊我也好想见一面喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.49,0:19:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.59,0:19:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的美人竟然是校医的老婆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.56,0:20:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道是该觉得可惜还是该觉得生气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.60,0:20:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.13,0:20:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和校医不是兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.31,0:20:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,池田同学，病装得如何了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.11,0:20:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是，没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.31,0:20:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了，一也还好吗？最近他很讨厌我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.72,0:20:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你爱捉弄他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.79,0:20:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.82,0:20:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他的反应很可爱让我不自觉就…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.19,0:20:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己弟弟那么可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.93,0:20:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可爱，可爱极了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.90,0:20:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔你真幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.30,0:20:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能结得了婚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.10,0:20:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.61,0:20:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你太太暑假有来宿舍吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.21,0:20:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一也
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.01,0:20:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从光流那里听来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.35,0:20:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被小堇抱住时流鼻血了是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.95,0:20:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你暂时不许给我回家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.12,0:20:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用你说，我也不会回去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.42,0:21:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕业之前，我绝对不会回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.49,0:21:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？阿莲寒假也不回去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.66,0:21:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.39,0:21:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.96,0:21:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过年时可以和漂亮的姊姊一起过耶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.23,0:21:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别对别人的老婆动歪脑筋喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.10,0:21:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不回去就是不回去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.14,0:21:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会留下来的请不要胡思乱想
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.21,0:21:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不，你一定会回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.18,0:21:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？为什么说得那么肯定？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.05,0:21:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.12,0:21:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒假不可以留下来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.18,0:21:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.95,0:21:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.75,0:21:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让职员在年末年初之际能放假回家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.32,0:21:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以宿舍会被关闭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.13,0:21:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…该怎办…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.80,0:21:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回家时想把机车留在房内这样没关系吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.47,0:21:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.77,0:21:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人可以从三楼把它扛走的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.94,0:21:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去校医的莲川老师叫我拿来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.74,0:21:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是会演戏
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.11,0:22:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还要我转告你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.65,0:22:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小堇很在意你圣诞节前会不会回家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.75,0:22:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.89,0:22:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕业前都不回家吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.02,0:22:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别那么意气用事快点回到有美人的家去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.76,0:22:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是残酷呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.93,0:22:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是对方什么都不知道不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.77,0:22:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这点残酷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.37,0:22:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是这个心的符号更是凶残
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.47,0:22:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙想到过寒假的方法了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.14,0:22:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小堇你这个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.28,0:22:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，住旅馆的话钱也不够
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.38,0:22:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有知道原因后愿意让你投靠的亲戚吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.32,0:22:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.12,0:22:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.36,0:22:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细想想我没有认识半个亲戚耶
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.43,0:22:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.83,0:22:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你哥的喜宴上应该有见过吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.46,0:22:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不，只有举行仪式，没有请客
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.53,0:22:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只有小堇的双亲来而已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.54,0:23:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的葬礼也是麻烦附近的邻居帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.17,0:23:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于爸爸，我也只看过照片
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.08,0:23:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.88,0:23:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我难道真的很倒楣吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.35,0:23:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且初恋情人嫁给了哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.42,0:23:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害得我不能回家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.09,0:23:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实在是太不幸了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.59,0:23:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行现在不是自怨自艾的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.23,0:23:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要想想怎么渡过这个寒假才行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.33,0:23:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莲川陷入泥沼之中？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.30,0:23:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，从昨天开始好像注意到了自己不幸的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.97,0:23:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.07,0:23:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直留到最后一天然后假装回家的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.18,0:23:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到宿舍关了之后再偷偷溜进来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.65,0:23:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能这么做了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.15,0:23:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没有暖气，太惨了啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.99,0:23:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.95,0:23:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要想想办法啦弄得人家真的很烦耶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.49,0:23:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你好像有烦恼喔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.10,0:24:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来我们的房间吧上帝会帮助你的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.47,0:24:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲，振作一点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.24,0:24:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果放着他不管看来他就会一直沉陷下去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.01,0:24:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.95,0:24:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能太宠他
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.45,0:24:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要让他当下届的宿舍长得锻炼他一下才行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.72,0:24:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道能撑多久
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.72,0:24:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不久就会复活了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.82,0:24:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不，我是说你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.66,0:24:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.06,0:24:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还是只能躲在宿舍里了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.73,0:24:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲个十天，应该没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.67,0:24:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小堇会很生气吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.57,0:24:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.24,0:24:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.74,0:24:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.88,0:24:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要来我家？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.38,0:24:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家是开旅馆的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.58,0:24:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不跟你收钱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.52,0:24:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有空房来我的房间就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.99,0:24:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.72,0:25:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一也，我嫁到你家好不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.87,0:25:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿莲，睡了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.94,0:25:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小瞬，我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.24,0:25:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要回家
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.14,0:25:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜…好冷喔
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.31,0:25:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.71,0:25:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是有事要去找隔壁的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.65,0:25:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔，已经不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.35,0:25:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要笑到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.33,0:25:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光流，我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.76,0:25:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来留到最后的人会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.93,0:25:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.90,0:25:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了，好好干吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.05,0:25:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.19,0:26:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.12,0:26:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要多吃一点喔
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.69,0:26:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为了小也，努力做了好多
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.43,0:26:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说小也会回来所以也没过圣诞节了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.10,0:26:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过年时一起去我的娘家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.16,0:26:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸妈很期待你去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.03,0:26:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，酒温好了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.57,0:26:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样？好吃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.17,0:26:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不好吃？
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.54,0:26:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回…回家真好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.17,0:26:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了与某人分亨珍贵的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.91,0:27:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以神赐给了我们际遇
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.75,0:27:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若拥有不装饰的微笑和些许勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.63,0:27:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是痛苦的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.10,0:27:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天也会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.50,0:27:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也来吧绿色的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.38,0:27:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然善解人意的人一个也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.62,0:27:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,We are the NO-Brand Heroes
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.33,0:27:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不输给太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.60,0:27:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,We are the NO-Brand Heroes
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.27,0:27:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满着光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.44,0:28:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥抱着世界上唯一的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.21,0:28:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只过了十天却觉得好怀念喔
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.75,0:28:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉回到自己的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.09,0:28:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这里是…这里是．
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.63,0:28:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是绿林寮
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.47,0:29:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（小渚再次出现）
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.94,0:29:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我遇到小渚了耶
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.61,0:29:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长，如果不小心点不知道又要发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.18,0:29:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧，不要紧阿忍他会想办法的，对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.55,0:29:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话先说在前面若又要我脱衣服，我可不干喔
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.02,0:29:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不就无法达成大家的期许了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.29,0:29:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊，光流学长
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.19,0:29:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这些家伙老是说一些风凉话
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.40,0:29:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样不知道究竟有什么阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.90,0:29:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖的小渚一步步逼近着绿林寮
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.20,0:29:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.81,0:29:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要突然插进来加油添醋啦


