[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00fffff1,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFGPOP1-W9,24,&H00fffff1,&H000000ff,&H00e7a65c,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,128
Style: edj,DFGPOP1-W9,22,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00d5a39e,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H0048103e,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,时尚中黑简体,27,&H00fffff1,&H000000ff,&H00e7a65c,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,18,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,时尚中黑简体,26,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00d5a39e,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.74,0:00:05.44,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}まっしろ　ページめくる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.09,0:00:13.63,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}飛び出す色と弾ける万華鏡の風景
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.27,0:00:15.61,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}気づけば
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.52,0:00:19.05,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ストーリーはまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:23.87,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ぎこちなく　始まったばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.94,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}深呼吸をもう一回
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.09,0:00:33.89,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}旅する風　包み込むように背中を押す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.04,0:00:42.05,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}あ　柔らかくて　暖かい君の手　握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.21,0:00:47.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}その心の奥まで届くように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:50.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}微笑んでくれたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:54.64,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}握り返してくれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.78,0:00:58.72,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}僕はただ前を見てる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.74,0:00:05.44,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}翻過這純白的一頁
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.09,0:00:13.63,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}映入眼睛的是萬花筒一般絢麗的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.27,0:00:15.61,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}等我發覺的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.52,0:00:19.05,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我們的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:23.87,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}才剛剛的開始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.94,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}再深呼吸一次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.09,0:00:33.89,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}風像是催促著我踏上旅途一樣 推著我前行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.04,0:00:42.05,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}啊 我握住你那柔軟而溫暖的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.21,0:00:47.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}希望我的心情能夠傳遞到你的心裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:50.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你用微笑回應我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:54.64,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你也握緊我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.78,0:00:58.72,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}那麼 我只需要一路前行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.07,0:01:04.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be2\blur1\3c&HE7BB9A&\c&H834131&}第三話 忘記吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.80,0:01:10.80,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}本片字幕由異域字幕組(www.yydm.com)製作,僅供試看之用,如果喜歡本作品,請購買並支持正版!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.96,0:01:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.98,0:01:15.98,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}翻譯 觸手 菜醬 諾 阿虛 校譯 阿虛 時間 阿虛 後期：風一樣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.16,0:01:14.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綠意盎然的季節到來了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.51,0:01:23.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.14,0:01:25.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直毫無根據的認為
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.25,0:01:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在男生中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.83,0:01:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是距離黑沼最近的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.50,0:01:33.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎也不見得是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.31,0:01:44.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那番話 到底是什麼意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.25,0:01:50.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我應該怎麼樣回答才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.11,0:01:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是忍不住這樣問自己
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.08,0:01:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風 風早說這番話是出於好意
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.81,0:02:00.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我卻一個人擅自在意起來...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.54,0:02:01.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還那種態度...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.08,0:02:08.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太失禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.63,0:02:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生氣了 就先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.55,0:02:14.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說啊 換做我肯定也是那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.33,0:02:18.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後 郵件緊接著就來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.75,0:02:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 給人的感覺是不是很糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.33,0:02:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望自己能不要太過介意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:50.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像以前一樣 自然的和風早相處
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.18,0:02:55.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前都是怎麼和風早相處的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.50,0:02:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經想不起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.52,0:03:00.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 風早
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.80,0:03:02.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天午休怎麼過
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.87,0:03:05.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天氣這麼好 到外面踢足球吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.31,0:03:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}讓你們見識一下的我新絕技
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.40,0:03:09.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早他們又要去踢足球啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.88,0:03:11.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中居跟根岸你們要不要一起來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.73,0:03:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.28,0:03:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們是足球部的嘛 技術一定很好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.14,0:03:17.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教教我頭球吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.68,0:03:19.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 當然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.43,0:03:20.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.88,0:03:27.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早 黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.48,0:03:31.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放輕鬆 自然地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.91,0:03:34.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早 早晨 好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.24,0:03:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.71,0:03:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.27,0:03:57.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早只不過是用與對待大家一樣的態度對待我而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.94,0:03:59.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.54,0:04:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說爽朗君不夠專業
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.06,0:04:08.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那種面帶笑容的招呼之後 還那麼盯著人家看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.24,0:04:10.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健人 你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.18,0:04:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.58,0:04:21.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天怎麼也是如此放鬆又自然的問候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.73,0:04:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早 早...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.54,0:04:27.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停 僵硬 太僵硬
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.90,0:04:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.87,0:04:33.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.85,0:04:34.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眉頭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.85,0:04:36.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.95,0:04:38.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該像這樣 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.25,0:04:39.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.13,0:04:41.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.05,0:04:47.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}早上好 早上好 早上好...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.50,0:04:42.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.40,0:04:44.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有興致
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.51,0:04:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們感情還真好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.47,0:04:53.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.88,0:04:57.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.41,0:05:02.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使都是出於好意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.59,0:05:09.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和風早的好意也肯定是有著不同的含義
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.55,0:05:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛 肚子好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.45,0:05:16.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近有點便秘
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.09,0:05:18.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 好痛苦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.51,0:05:25.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 爽子去哪裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.66,0:05:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廁所吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.31,0:05:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能治便秘
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.48,0:05:33.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.51,0:05:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該怎麼處理這東西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.55,0:05:37.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又開始...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.59,0:05:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的研究了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.44,0:05:42.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.19,0:05:44.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,預備
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.70,0:05:54.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什麼事了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.09,0:05:56.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你最近沒什麼精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.32,0:05:59.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.58,0:06:00.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.79,0:06:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 下一組
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.52,0:06:07.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在想 她剛剛進入新的班級
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.47,0:06:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在努力著融入其中的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.91,0:06:13.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是不該對她說那種話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.67,0:06:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該讓她露出那麼困惑的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.38,0:06:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.70,0:06:21.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.39,0:06:24.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種話？什麼話？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.86,0:06:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要問
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.12,0:06:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任性
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.62,0:06:30.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.01,0:06:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我基本就是非常任性
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.59,0:06:35.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡自說自話 而且獨佔欲很強
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.03,0:06:37.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有急性子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.89,0:06:40.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 忍耐也已經快到極限了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.08,0:06:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使知道她會很為難
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.94,0:06:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望能讓她立刻瞭解我的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.11,0:06:47.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.16,0:06:49.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有嗎...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.87,0:06:50.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.07,0:06:54.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不想讓她為難
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.48,0:07:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她付出了那麼多努力 才走到今天這一步
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.60,0:07:07.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說 對方估計也喜歡翔太你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.37,0:07:12.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是沒有被討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.14,0:07:14.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\pos(747,413)}收\N到\N 人\N情\N 巧\N克\N力\N的\N人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.52,0:07:14.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\pos(52,338)}沒\N收\N到\N巧\N克\N力\N的\N人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.90,0:07:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\frz9.5\pos(455,283)}不\N知\N道\N為\N啥\N也\N收\N到\N巧\N克\N力\N的\N人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.92,0:07:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早好爽朗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.68,0:07:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.60,0:07:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.64,0:07:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.66,0:07:35.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡爽朗了 鬼知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.28,0:07:38.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰也沒那麼說...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.67,0:07:44.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是在著急啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.57,0:07:46.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然著急了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.58,0:07:51.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定其他人也發現了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.51,0:07:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到很快其他男生也會喜歡上她
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.31,0:08:01.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就很不安
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.88,0:08:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就那麼好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.68,0:08:10.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我看來她就像是個小芥子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.35,0:08:10.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs24}小芥子是一種木製人偶 留著和爽子一樣的髮型
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.62,0:08:14.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我不太明白 但你好辛苦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.07,0:08:16.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得這句話很讓人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.70,0:08:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子去哪裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.80,0:08:31.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的話 小千和綾音也一起一起來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.21,0:08:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎來到我的藥草角
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.21,0:08:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些名牌到底是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.42,0:08:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得寫上名牌會對大家比較有用
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.36,0:08:49.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過一般不是應該把藥草的名字列出來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.44,0:08:52.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想把功能寫上 這樣更能一目瞭然
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.43,0:08:56.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些與其說是功能 倒是更像會導致便秘拉肚子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.58,0:08:57.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.60,0:09:00.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被詛咒的名牌和藥草
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.39,0:09:03.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果加上功能和作用呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.03,0:09:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字好小
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.88,0:09:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利尿作用？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.65,0:09:14.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,KENT
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.87,0:09:18.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經直接叫我的名字啦 好高興呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.97,0:09:24.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為是風早 稍稍期待...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.35,0:09:26.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛剛有期待了一下吧 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.29,0:09:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以為是自己喜歡的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.03,0:09:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是超能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.86,0:09:36.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.80,0:09:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不僅自然 又感覺良好...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.30,0:09:43.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是超能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.67,0:09:45.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 你的表情太僵硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.23,0:09:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子的表情不可以那麼僵硬
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.31,0:09:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我基本上來說屬於博愛主義
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.04,0:09:57.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些放棄自己幸福的女生 我是不能置之不理的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.25,0:10:02.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事鬼知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.92,0:10:04.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放棄？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.47,0:10:06.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.50,0:10:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我這樣的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.08,0:10:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才那是什麼 錯覺嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.66,0:10:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得有矢野這樣的模範女人在身邊 是吧 綾音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.50,0:10:23.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 還有太近了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.22,0:10:26.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便說下 吉田的腿好美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.59,0:10:31.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.43,0:10:42.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的僵硬到清爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.04,0:10:46.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 你不要勉強她笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.47,0:10:47.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為會很恐怖的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.20,0:10:51.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.77,0:10:56.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想讓自己感覺正常一點 師父
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.38,0:10:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,師父？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.69,0:11:01.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,師父嗎？不壞的稱呼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.22,0:11:03.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會加油的 超能力師父
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.90,0:11:04.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眉頭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.75,0:11:08.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}超能力和師父要分開叫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.44,0:11:10.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙 到底想幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.48,0:11:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}是 超能力的師父
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.11,0:11:13.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.11,0:11:15.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好久不見
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.08,0:11:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的班級怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.08,0:11:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可愛的女生嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.06,0:11:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與其說是可愛 倒不如說是讓人在意的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.04,0:11:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 是什麼樣的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.07,0:11:27.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灰暗僵硬的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.45,0:11:28.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.39,0:11:33.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.62,0:11:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 綾音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.29,0:11:38.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底有什麼企圖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.25,0:11:40.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,企圖？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.61,0:11:42.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嗎？為什麼這樣說
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.71,0:11:46.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得你經常喜歡去招惹爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.84,0:11:51.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為貞子喜歡風早吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.35,0:11:54.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然猜對了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.81,0:11:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 等一下 不要做多餘的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.14,0:11:59.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是那孩子最關鍵的時期
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.48,0:12:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最關鍵的時期嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.21,0:12:07.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題 我是個好人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.70,0:12:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.64,0:12:16.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.76,0:12:30.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡期中考試會考到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.96,0:12:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 這就期中了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.71,0:12:35.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.61,0:12:41.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 聽說一年級的時候B班流傳過貞子的詛咒筆記
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.78,0:12:43.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是什麼詛咒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.46,0:12:46.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為有那個 班級平均成績才大漲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.09,0:12:47.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.12,0:12:48.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的真的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.93,0:12:50.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥啥 貞子在期中考試時...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.39,0:12:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,筆記的詛咒...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.71,0:12:54.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個提高分數的詛咒?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.07,0:12:55.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對不對 是降福的詛咒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.94,0:12:58.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡 說不定期中也會考到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.48,0:13:01.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 這是說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.56,0:13:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子的筆記 在期中考試時幫了大忙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.17,0:13:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是挺有成績的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.10,0:13:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成績
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.52,0:13:12.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也會考...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.12,0:13:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同學們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.53,0:13:18.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子說 今天放學之後要開期中複習講座
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.08,0:13:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,復 複習講座...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.83,0:13:30.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種了不得的事情 由我來做...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.99,0:13:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題吧 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.21,0:13:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在上課啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.94,0:13:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.44,0:13:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果大家覺得我可以的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.63,0:13:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼故事至少也能講上三個
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.56,0:13:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會辜負大家的期望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.04,0:13:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想大家沒有那方面的期望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.38,0:13:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經來了四個了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.32,0:13:59.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 你真是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.47,0:14:01.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有複習講座 真是得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.46,0:14:02.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.43,0:14:05.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後呢 提議的健人反而消失了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.98,0:14:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經開始了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.61,0:14:15.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 剛剛要開始
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.16,0:14:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好趕上了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.70,0:14:24.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.46,0:14:25.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也來了啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.67,0:14:28.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.81,0:14:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值日剛剛做完
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.44,0:14:31.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠你了啊 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.47,0:14:38.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是呢 請大家多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.27,0:14:40.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 已經開始了?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.24,0:14:41.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高橋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.87,0:14:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛聽風早說的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.42,0:14:49.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.45,0:14:50.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}去棒球部了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.31,0:14:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是風早...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.94,0:14:55.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.92,0:14:58.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}就先從數學開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.72,0:14:57.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會好好努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.57,0:15:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管不知道我能不能幫到大家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.69,0:15:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 還真來了不少人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.32,0:15:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛風早不是到處拉人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.67,0:15:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個爽朗君?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.53,0:15:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都說 風早不會對受到孤立的同學置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.89,0:15:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.81,0:15:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶴也一起參加下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.17,0:15:28.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先在這個範圍內要記住的 這個公式
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.26,0:15:30.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 看不見啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.60,0:15:33.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 還是用黑板講吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.37,0:15:35.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑 黑...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.32,0:15:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 那樣記筆記也方便
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.15,0:15:41.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 別掙扎了 快去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.42,0:15:43.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.06,0:16:25.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.62,0:16:26.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答案是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.71,0:16:28.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5根2
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.58,0:16:31.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜二人組居然解出正確答案了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.66,0:16:33.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為爽子講的很容易理解嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.56,0:16:35.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.84,0:16:40.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是這裡嘛 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.61,0:16:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭一次看到貞子笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:16:59.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來貞子也會笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.13,0:17:03.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子的笑可以招來福運的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.51,0:17:05.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我看到過哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.38,0:17:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的話 可是看過好多次了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.81,0:17:09.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始顯擺了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.62,0:17:13.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到貞子笑 真是賺到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.74,0:17:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,數學題也解決了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.65,0:17:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能來這次的複習講座 真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.77,0:17:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回見
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.89,0:17:45.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你了 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.51,0:17:46.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有機會再教我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.09,0:17:47.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.27,0:17:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是 非常感謝各位
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.11,0:17:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.34,0:17:56.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子 只要努力一下 即使是做不來的事情也能做好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.08,0:17:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,師父 今天謝謝您了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.64,0:18:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 有戲有戲 絕對有戲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.42,0:18:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,螞蟻？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.42,0:18:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}此處 讀音相近
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.09,0:18:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你能先回去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.79,0:18:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還有事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.93,0:18:27.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很重要的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:31.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.35,0:18:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能跟你談談嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.94,0:18:37.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 我們還有急事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.81,0:18:43.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘記了嗎 你不是要去看連衣裙嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.48,0:18:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 對哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.15,0:18:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼爽子 我們先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.17,0:18:49.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.39,0:19:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要更自然...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.91,0:19:10.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更自然地向他道謝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.68,0:19:12.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.66,0:19:17.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撞上了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.25,0:19:18.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 你先說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.31,0:19:21.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.28,0:19:26.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 今天...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.22,0:19:30.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 非常感謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.92,0:19:35.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本想更好地表達自己的謝意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.01,0:19:37.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻無法好好說出口
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.14,0:19:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明如此的高興
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.38,0:19:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我也覺得我不太適合站在人群面前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.12,0:19:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.99,0:19:50.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得很合適
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.50,0:19:56.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得 你很擅長指導別人學習
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.32,0:20:04.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.47,0:20:07.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惟獨不想...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.60,0:20:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被風早同學討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.13,0:20:23.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天 我所說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.02,0:20:29.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必在意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.78,0:20:35.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.79,0:21:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.21,0:21:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你好久了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:26.80,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}どうか今だけは振り向かないで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.34,0:21:39.77,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}夕暮れさわぐ風　触れそうな距離
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.29,0:21:52.80,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君を見つめてる　ずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.28,0:21:59.06,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで　
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:05.71,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:11.53,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}叶わない恋でもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.67,0:22:14.85,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}傷ついてもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.01,0:22:19.74,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}何度でも伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.00,0:22:23.61,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君に届け
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:26.80,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}這一刻 請你不要回頭看我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.34,0:21:39.77,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}在傍晚搖曳的風中 近在咫尺的距離
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.29,0:21:52.80,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我一直 凝視著你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.28,0:21:59.06,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}喜歡你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:05.71,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}一直喜歡著你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:11.53,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使這份戀情永遠也不能實現
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.67,0:22:14.85,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使會讓我受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.01,0:22:19.74,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我也想一次又一次的讓你感受到這份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.00,0:22:23.61,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.02,0:22:34.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\3c&H000007&\c&HF3F3F3&\pos(578,339)\fn汉仪丫丫体简}第四話 不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.06,0:22:29.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不經意間 太過在意
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.67,0:22:31.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愈演愈烈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.37,0:22:34.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集 不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:24:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H904F0D&\3c&HE1CFCA&\be3\fs20\pos(823,371)\fad(450,450)}異\N域\N字\N幕\N組\N長\N期\N招\N募\N翻\N譯\N校\N譯\N人\N員
