[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00FFFFF1,&H000000FF,&H00E1C4EE,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFGPOP1-W9,24,&H00FFFFF1,&H000000FF,&H00E7A65C,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edj,DFGPOP1-W9,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00D5A39E,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0048103E,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,时尚中黑简体,27,&H00FFFFF1,&H000000FF,&H00E7A65C,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,时尚中黑简体,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00D5A39E,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.54,0:00:05.24,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}まっしろ　ページめくる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.54,0:00:05.24,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}翻过这纯白的一页
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.89,0:00:13.43,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}飛び出す色と弾ける万華鏡の風景
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.89,0:00:13.43,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}映入眼睛的是万花筒一般绚丽的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.07,0:00:15.41,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}気づけば
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.07,0:00:15.41,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}等我发觉的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.32,0:00:18.85,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ストーリーはまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.32,0:00:18.85,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我们的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:23.67,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ぎこちなく　始まったばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:23.67,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}才刚刚的开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.74,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}深呼吸をもう一回
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.74,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}再深呼吸一次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.89,0:00:33.69,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}旅する風　包み込むように背中を押す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.89,0:00:33.69,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}风像是催促着我踏上旅途一样 推着我前行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.84,0:00:41.85,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}あ　柔らかくて　暖かい君の手　握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.84,0:00:41.85,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}啊 我握住你那柔软而温暖的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:47.02,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}その心の奥まで届くように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:47.02,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}希望我的心情能够传递到你的心里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.17,0:00:50.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}微笑んでくれたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.17,0:00:50.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你用微笑回应我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.41,0:00:54.44,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}握り返してくれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.41,0:00:54.44,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你也握紧我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.58,0:00:58.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}僕はただ前を見てる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.58,0:00:58.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}那么 我只需要一路前行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:01:04.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be2\blur1\3c&HE7BB9A&\c&H834131&}第十话 从这里开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.80,0:01:10.80,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}本片字幕由异域字幕组(www.yydm.com)制作,仅供试看之用,如果喜欢本作品,请购买并支持正版!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.59,0:01:10.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 已经这个时间了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.81,0:01:16.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间过得太快了 一眨眼就...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.98,0:01:15.98,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}翻译 阿虚 校译 时间 阿虚 后期：风一样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.24,0:01:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.21,0:01:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有化妆队列的个人表演
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.69,0:01:27.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找个地方去小睡一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.94,0:01:29.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.07,0:01:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.33,0:01:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使不做这些事 我今夜也肯定无法入睡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.21,0:01:42.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他东西要缝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.53,0:01:44.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.20,0:01:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 手机 是不是在闪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.43,0:01:54.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢 是爸爸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.36,0:02:07.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漫长 漫长的一夜...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.23,0:02:26.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.79,0:02:29.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结衣喜欢安藤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.61,0:02:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错 不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.13,0:02:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs28}安藤君 风早的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.45,0:02:34.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安藤是个好人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.32,0:02:36.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.61,0:02:38.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.10,0:02:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我也让佑辅去试探了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.48,0:02:45.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贞子怎么看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.30,0:02:49.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请 请直说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.92,0:02:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直说...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.35,0:03:07.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好 我觉得 非常完美
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.76,0:03:10.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.38,0:03:14.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吧 说你们很配呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.09,0:03:17.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是黑魔法的贞子说的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.61,0:03:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 说了不负责任的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.92,0:03:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那我就努力看看吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.46,0:03:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像从贞子那里得到力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.01,0:03:39.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.02,0:03:40.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啦没啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.98,0:03:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是同伴意识罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.21,0:03:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 明天就是终点了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.87,0:03:50.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好漫长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.76,0:03:54.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在风早想找爽子却找不到 肯定很着急吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.58,0:04:08.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么今天要做花车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.24,0:04:11.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为明天要化妆游行嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.99,0:04:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为进度落后太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.15,0:04:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那边的城没搞清楚到底该做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.48,0:04:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.10,0:04:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次又一次...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.26,0:04:27.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回想着同样的场景
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.04,0:04:41.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让自己明白 那些事情 并不是梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.68,0:04:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}再好好谈一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.95,0:04:57.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.21,0:05:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭 第二天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.75,0:05:18.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小千 准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.29,0:05:20.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 就剩下把蛇缠上了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.54,0:05:21.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.44,0:05:25.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野正在准备
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.69,0:05:29.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 忍着不要眨眼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.21,0:05:31.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.22,0:05:33.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 弄好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.58,0:05:35.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚弄好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.18,0:05:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看过我们班的女生没
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.04,0:05:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了看了 超可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.29,0:05:46.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 衣服好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.19,0:05:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很适合你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.96,0:05:58.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.59,0:05:59.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.04,0:06:02.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住想要确认下 到底有没有脚...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.76,0:06:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来想给她化点眼影或者涂下指甲的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.07,0:06:08.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是姑且重视一下震撼力...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.28,0:06:13.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贞子是番町屋敷的菊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.00,0:06:15.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高桥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.67,0:06:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是和井联系在一起的 所以觉得和贞子有点像
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.85,0:06:26.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法再相信男人的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.37,0:06:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和得不到信任而暴走了的男人之间的爱憎剧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.85,0:06:33.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那样的故事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.64,0:06:36.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可以这样解释啦 不错的角色嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.02,0:06:40.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊 高桥 胡子很适合你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.31,0:06:45.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花车和衣服都赶上了 真是万幸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.21,0:06:49.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 为什么龙一副没睡醒的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.44,0:06:52.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为 成长期吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.26,0:06:56.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七个小矮人吗 C班干得不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.12,0:06:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样穿可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.92,0:07:01.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道 随便吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.53,0:07:05.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野 我这护身符的打扮怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.15,0:07:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很适合嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.98,0:07:10.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一副傻样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.80,0:07:12.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.43,0:07:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千鹤是格斗家吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.34,0:07:16.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 是蛇系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.47,0:07:18.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很合适嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.27,0:07:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.34,0:07:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.93,0:07:23.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.17,0:07:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才在楼梯被千草叫走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.22,0:07:28.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thank You
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.40,0:07:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.05,0:07:35.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿的那件衣服是爽子缝的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.19,0:07:43.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 差不多到时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.04,0:07:47.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好的人到外面排好队
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.64,0:07:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.63,0:07:49.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.88,0:07:51.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼不在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.28,0:07:53.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼已经出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.87,0:07:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.32,0:07:59.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么 又去被甩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.42,0:08:02.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你管我啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.92,0:08:09.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞳孔放大 兴奋版的风早
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.65,0:08:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明之前还一副垂头丧气的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.45,0:08:14.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别废话啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.28,0:08:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快让开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.16,0:08:29.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,个人表演 要像昨天说的一样加油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.28,0:08:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太也一定很期待的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.20,0:08:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.24,0:09:00.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为这样 我才不想你被别人看到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.24,0:09:06.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天...谢谢你的邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.70,0:09:09.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我才是呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.91,0:09:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早 你看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.47,0:09:15.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跳来跳去的话 会更受欢迎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.96,0:09:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.03,0:09:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我想和黑沼说话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.66,0:09:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和黑沼再一次好好地...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.89,0:09:44.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些话想要对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.98,0:09:56.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以让我先说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.89,0:10:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要在 在勇气消失之前...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.31,0:10:13.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新年参拜的时候 我真的好幸福...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.78,0:10:20.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 因为太幸福 反而觉得害怕...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.41,0:10:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既想着要独占风早
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.93,0:10:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却又唯独不想被风早讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.97,0:10:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心如果把自己的心意说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.36,0:10:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人的关系会就此结束
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.53,0:10:42.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.94,0:10:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望从这里开始和风早建立新的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.79,0:10:53.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里重新开始
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.91,0:10:59.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.99,0:11:02.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算新的开始...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.73,0:11:07.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也一定 一定会...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.38,0:11:12.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是和风早一起的话 一定会...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.68,0:11:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集合
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.24,0:11:19.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.68,0:11:22.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.78,0:11:26.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和风早相遇之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.92,0:11:28.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许多事情都改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.35,0:11:32.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为过去一年的最终成果
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.47,0:11:36.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定用最好的演技 把怨念全都表现出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.09,0:11:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定能帮到大家的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.90,0:11:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢上风早之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.59,0:12:00.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.86,0:12:10.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.86,0:12:21.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.28,0:13:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那句话 我应该怎么理解才好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.58,0:13:24.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在称赞你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.79,0:13:30.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要和大家开心的在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.95,0:13:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能和她们成为朋友...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.35,0:13:56.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.28,0:14:12.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使你不为我做什么也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.08,0:14:15.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.23,0:14:57.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一组是 二年级D班
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.45,0:15:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.13,0:15:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.97,0:15:20.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 盘子...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.73,0:15:31.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论数多少次 总是少了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.98,0:15:37.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这里 动手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.61,0:15:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经冰过了 很凉的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.93,0:15:59.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 请喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.15,0:16:02.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是贿赂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.11,0:16:04.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是贿赂了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.09,0:16:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太吓人了 请不要看这边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.07,0:16:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 第43届北幌高中学园祭闭幕仪式正式开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.16,0:16:48.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先进行的是各部门的名次发表
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.08,0:16:51.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墙报新闻部门 第一名是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.83,0:16:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年B班的西部片
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.98,0:17:02.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,模拟店部门 第一名 二年D班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.01,0:17:10.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑魔法咨询大获好评 第一名名至实归
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.27,0:17:20.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}贞子 贞子 贞子...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.15,0:17:18.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是化妆队列名次的发表
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.28,0:17:20.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错 有戏
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.59,0:17:28.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二年B班在表演中送给裁判的饮料被认为是贿赂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.06,0:17:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化妆队列的得分被判为0
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.46,0:17:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特此通知
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.98,0:17:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是大家期待已久的综合成绩排名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.97,0:17:49.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.96,0:17:51.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁管你啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.60,0:17:52.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.57,0:17:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥的良苦用心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.70,0:17:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用心啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.02,0:18:06.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.79,0:18:11.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果综合只得了个第六啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.15,0:18:14.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是二年级里也是第一了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.02,0:18:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可惜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.95,0:18:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是没有贿赂的话 化妆队列也算不错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.91,0:18:23.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贞子的演技太逼真了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.89,0:18:26.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庆功宴还是在老地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.96,0:18:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.92,0:18:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.58,0:18:59.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有区别的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.69,0:19:02.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一样的 没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.58,0:19:08.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管一直怀疑着到底会怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.49,0:19:11.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却也没有放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.79,0:19:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终发现了这个可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.37,0:19:17.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.61,0:19:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.85,0:19:42.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要的是 风早的全部...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.28,0:19:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.71,0:20:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是做梦一样...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.57,0:20:16.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于传达到了...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.08,0:21:14.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比任何人 都要喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:26.70,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}どうか今だけは振り向かないで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:26.70,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}这一刻 请你不要回头看我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.24,0:21:39.67,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}夕暮れさわぐ風　触れそうな距離
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.24,0:21:39.67,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}在傍晚摇曳的风中 近在咫尺的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.19,0:21:52.70,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君を見つめてる　ずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.19,0:21:52.70,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我一直 凝视着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.18,0:21:58.96,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.18,0:21:58.96,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.90,0:22:05.61,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.90,0:22:05.61,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}一直喜欢着你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.58,0:22:11.43,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}叶わない恋でもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.58,0:22:11.43,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使这份恋情永远也不能实现
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.57,0:22:14.75,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}傷ついてもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.57,0:22:14.75,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使会让我受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.91,0:22:19.64,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}何度でも伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.91,0:22:19.64,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我也想一次又一次的让你感受到这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.90,0:22:23.51,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君に届け
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.90,0:22:23.51,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}好想告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.99,0:22:34.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\3c&H000007&\c&HF3F3F3&\pos(578,339)\fn汉仪丫丫体简}第十一话 学园祭之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.66,0:22:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通红的侧脸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.97,0:22:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细语的海风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.68,0:22:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话 学园祭之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:24:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H904F0D&\3c&HE1CFCA&\be3\fs20\pos(823,371)\fad(450,450)}异\N域\N字\N幕\N组\N长\N期\N招\N募\N翻\N译\N校\N译\N人\N员

