[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00FFFFF1,&H000000FF,&H00E1C4EE,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFGPOP1-W9,24,&H00FFFFF1,&H000000FF,&H00E7A65C,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edj,DFGPOP1-W9,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00D5A39E,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0048103E,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,时尚中黑简体,27,&H00FFFFF1,&H000000FF,&H00E7A65C,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,时尚中黑简体,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00D5A39E,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.74,0:00:05.44,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}まっしろ　ページめくる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.09,0:00:13.63,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}飛び出す色と弾ける万華鏡の風景
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.27,0:00:15.61,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}気づけば
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.52,0:00:19.05,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ストーリーはまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:23.87,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ぎこちなく　始まったばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.94,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}深呼吸をもう一回
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.09,0:00:33.89,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}旅する風　包み込むように背中を押す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.04,0:00:42.05,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}あ　柔らかくて　暖かい君の手　握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.21,0:00:47.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}その心の奥まで届くように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:50.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}微笑んでくれたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:54.64,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}握り返してくれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.78,0:00:58.72,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}僕はただ前を見てる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.74,0:00:05.44,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}翻过这纯白的一页
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.09,0:00:13.63,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}映入眼睛的是万花筒一般绚丽的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.27,0:00:15.61,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}等我发觉的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.52,0:00:19.05,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我们的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:23.87,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}才刚刚的开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.94,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}再深呼吸一次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.09,0:00:33.89,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}风像是催促着我踏上旅途一样 推着我前行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.04,0:00:42.05,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}啊 我握住你那柔软而温暖的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.21,0:00:47.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}希望我的心情能够传递到你的心里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:50.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你用微笑回应我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:54.64,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你也握紧我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.78,0:00:58.72,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}那么 我只需要一路前行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.07,0:01:05.08,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be2\blur1\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HE7BB9A&}第一话  情人节
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.80,0:01:10.80,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}本片字幕由异域字幕组(www.yydm.com)制作,仅供试看之用,如果喜欢本作品,请购买并支持正版!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.98,0:01:15.98,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}翻译：菜酱 触手 阿虚 诺 校译：阿虚 时间：阿虚 后期：风一样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.29,0:01:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的也好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.02,0:01:57.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.52,0:01:59.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 绫音不嫌弃的话也请吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.33,0:02:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.64,0:02:03.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为回礼给你这个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.21,0:02:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.86,0:02:08.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 新的座位还习惯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.50,0:02:09.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.93,0:02:13.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒假完结了之后的一月
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.92,0:02:15.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换座位了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.48,0:02:18.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道是不是我的错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.37,0:02:21.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在我后面的高桥同学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.25,0:02:26.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上课的时候都会捉弄我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.74,0:02:30.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在旁边的八木君
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.85,0:02:32.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔会跟我搭话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.25,0:02:36.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经常会有鬼压床的感觉 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.47,0:02:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.02,0:02:39.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.05,0:02:43.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和以前不同 已经不太会被人躲着了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.63,0:02:45.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是很好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.61,0:02:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是托大家福
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.52,0:02:50.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了 爽子的感谢时间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.32,0:02:56.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使换座位了 也不表示一切回到原点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.48,0:02:56.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}这个好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.90,0:02:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}是吧是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.04,0:03:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都在继续
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.97,0:03:03.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.83,0:03:05.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.31,0:03:06.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.60,0:03:09.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的吧 真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.04,0:03:11.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.79,0:03:15.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说完全不寂寞的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.55,0:03:16.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.19,0:03:22.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她都不怎么笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.35,0:03:23.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.08,0:03:33.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 是贞子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.14,0:03:38.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 贞子那样也算是开朗了很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.87,0:03:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太也没有用了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.99,0:03:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.07,0:03:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟风早的距离...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.10,0:03:53.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是接近了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.55,0:04:04.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过换了座位之后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.66,0:04:09.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又似乎又疏远了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.69,0:04:14.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后到了二月
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.58,0:04:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我虽然不怎么吃甜的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.45,0:04:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送礼物给我的话还是收下的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.15,0:04:24.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天是情人节
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.86,0:04:28.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子打算买还是做
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.03,0:04:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.86,0:04:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛吓一跳啊 反正你也是每年都要送给爸爸的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.66,0:04:38.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸 爸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.28,0:04:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.51,0:04:42.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会送给龙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.33,0:04:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.42,0:04:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛 用来贿赂人也许不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.69,0:04:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 贿赂是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.05,0:04:50.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.17,0:04:53.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,材料已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.48,0:05:04.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是绫音的份
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.52,0:05:08.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边是给小千和真田的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.51,0:05:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是朋美的 这是小悦的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.79,0:05:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是爸爸的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.45,0:05:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.73,0:05:28.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还 还是不要写卡片了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.77,0:05:41.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看一下 只有风早的果仁特别多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.77,0:05:47.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 这些心形的装饰也放了好多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.85,0:05:51.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意识间偏心了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.12,0:05:54.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是手制的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.34,0:05:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为想给他手制的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.29,0:06:04.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一直以来的谢礼会不会太隆重了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.00,0:06:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.35,0:06:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是想送给他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.12,0:06:20.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.46,0:06:41.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.78,0:06:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.43,0:06:49.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那是巧克力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.74,0:06:52.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.49,0:07:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回 回见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.82,0:07:05.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.31,0:07:18.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没送出手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.35,0:07:22.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.87,0:07:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和真田一起吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.98,0:07:25.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.85,0:07:26.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.00,0:07:28.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 贞子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.77,0:07:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还蛮不错的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.05,0:07:33.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能那么地高兴收下真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.88,0:07:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.99,0:07:38.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}风早 有巧克力吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.57,0:07:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}太好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.02,0:07:39.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.49,0:07:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.12,0:07:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是人情的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.41,0:07:44.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是人情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.65,0:07:46.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他高兴成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.05,0:07:53.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去一下厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.53,0:07:56.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.33,0:08:05.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经紧张到不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.05,0:08:09.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说风早从早上开始就已经收到两份巧克力了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.79,0:08:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我也给他了 他的血糖会不会升高
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.09,0:08:19.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就算一天吃不完 只要放到冰箱的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.98,0:08:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不要担心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.87,0:08:26.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像刚才那样 自然的送给他的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.86,0:08:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早也会爽快的接受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.69,0:08:32.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早 送你巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.89,0:08:33.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thank You
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.94,0:08:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像更不自然了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.80,0:08:45.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 就像送给小千和绫音一样普通的...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.95,0:08:49.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通的？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:51.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.06,0:08:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 一想到是给风早巧克力就在意的不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.40,0:09:05.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙也收到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.11,0:09:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.26,0:09:08.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.16,0:09:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个貌似和刚刚吃的不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.00,0:09:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我吃没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.24,0:09:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是本命？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.52,0:09:19.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.95,0:09:21.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千鹤她刚才...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.69,0:09:22.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吉田做的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.10,0:09:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.09,0:09:26.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑沼的亲手做的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.98,0:09:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是从千鹤那里分到的人情巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.63,0:09:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咋了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.23,0:09:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样的巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.76,0:09:43.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 想吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.76,0:09:45.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊 给
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.57,0:09:46.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.40,0:09:47.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.58,0:09:49.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人找你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.87,0:09:58.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我想的太多了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.65,0:10:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是他还是坐在我前面的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.65,0:10:04.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以在送给大家的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.15,0:10:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺势自然的给他了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.36,0:10:25.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没 看到没
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.90,0:10:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是拒绝了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.09,0:10:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.70,0:10:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.54,0:10:35.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 还会被拒绝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.44,0:10:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那肯定不是 人情巧克力了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.10,0:10:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}起因是斤斤计较和误会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.10,0:10:56.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}妄想以此为起点...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.18,0:10:56.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才他之所以会若无其事的收下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.88,0:10:59.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是因为那只是人情巧克力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.14,0:11:03.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了感谢他才送巧克力的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.43,0:11:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢礼算是人情巧克力？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.51,0:11:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友情巧克力？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.18,0:11:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪 虽然没有打算告白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.03,0:11:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我的确喜欢着风早
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.36,0:11:23.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情况下 到底应该是什么巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.79,0:11:25.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是拒绝了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.60,0:11:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 突然认清了现实
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.11,0:11:41.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想送给他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.73,0:11:46.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要给的话 就得快点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.60,0:11:50.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回过神来 就已经放学了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.20,0:11:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近迷上了重播的电视剧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.98,0:11:57.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 外国的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.91,0:11:59.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 是偶像剧啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.05,0:12:04.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 你到底送没送出去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.92,0:12:07.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似没看到啥迹象
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.23,0:12:11.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 回家吧 矢野 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.43,0:12:12.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.30,0:12:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 找地方玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.37,0:12:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和女朋友有约
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.29,0:12:21.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}我再坚持下 一个人回家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.02,0:12:20.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.52,0:12:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.09,0:12:28.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你份美差 给我走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.63,0:12:31.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.16,0:12:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们先回吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.84,0:12:35.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.31,0:12:36.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.99,0:12:38.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.75,0:12:41.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会留在学校里...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.36,0:12:51.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这或许是最后的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.96,0:12:54.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 还是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.06,0:12:58.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.73,0:13:04.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微再等一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.18,0:13:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们陪你好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.54,0:13:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}嗯嗯 这样也不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.58,0:13:11.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那明天见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.00,0:13:13.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.22,0:13:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说 城从刚才开始就盯着矢野...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.34,0:13:18.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘 不能和他的视线对上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.15,0:13:22.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 啥 啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.80,0:13:31.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下来了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.16,0:13:34.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.01,0:13:36.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.83,0:13:41.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近肩膀僵的厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.64,0:13:43.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你用力点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.33,0:13:46.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会就为了这么点破事...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.31,0:13:49.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的光荣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.02,0:13:52.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想做的话也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.52,0:13:56.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前你在大雨中哭着跑来我家的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.46,0:13:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}(风早 8岁)
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.51,0:14:01.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是爸爸让我送来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.61,0:14:03.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕下雨吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.63,0:14:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭着喊着要住在我家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.82,0:14:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}(风早 6岁)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.62,0:14:10.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果给我把床尿了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.15,0:14:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.97,0:14:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个死小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.60,0:14:15.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍照留念吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.62,0:14:17.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情 那种事情 这种事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.93,0:14:18.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在校内放送上给你...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.64,0:14:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦 知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.71,0:14:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错不错 特别是左肩和脖子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.63,0:14:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.41,0:14:32.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.38,0:14:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是巧克力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.45,0:14:38.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了我这种程度 粉丝赶都赶不走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.50,0:14:42.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来只是为了炫耀一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.68,0:14:44.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人头痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.42,0:14:47.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}(平时受您关照了)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.31,0:14:49.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个袋子里的巧克力 该不会是黑沼的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.29,0:14:51.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.77,0:14:56.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来岂不是毁了女孩子的一番心意吗 我怎么会做那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.66,0:14:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要嫉妒啊 那就太难看了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.12,0:15:03.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 那里是骨头诶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.42,0:15:07.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左肩和脖子 是不是遭报应了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:10.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在漫画上看到过
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.68,0:15:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脖子以上都和神明有关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.35,0:15:16.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神明...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.72,0:15:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在神社对着神木发火
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.33,0:15:23.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一毛钱都不捐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}反正也没钱 就这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.53,0:15:32.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶快吃黑沼的巧克力驱一下邪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.58,0:15:33.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整袋全吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.45,0:15:37.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噎住了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.17,0:15:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太 水 水
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.99,0:16:24.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要交给他的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.74,0:16:28.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有趁现在了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.54,0:16:31.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.71,0:16:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.65,0:16:39.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 胡桃泽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.35,0:16:45.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的一个情人节 你就收下作纪念吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.94,0:16:48.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是如此应该无所谓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.20,0:16:50.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是最初也是最后的一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.07,0:17:02.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.75,0:17:32.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷窥吗 真是恶趣味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.69,0:17:34.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.71,0:17:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是稍微 确实 可能有点在意...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.40,0:17:38.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然承认了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.17,0:17:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早他好像不收本命巧克力哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.17,0:17:56.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 胡桃你送的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.78,0:17:58.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是特别的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.39,0:18:03.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经是被甩掉的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.42,0:18:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很特别 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.23,0:18:15.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 是送给风早的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.07,0:18:18.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是...为了答谢他至今为止一直帮助我...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.06,0:18:20.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.83,0:18:23.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说过不敢奢望交往什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.14,0:18:26.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真的只是谢礼而已吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.96,0:18:32.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你还是带着些侥幸的心理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.22,0:18:40.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那巧克力 如果是人情巧克力的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.02,0:18:43.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早一定会收下的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.92,0:18:49.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不后悔的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.37,0:18:51.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.75,0:18:56.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只是这种程度的使坏就能让她放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.35,0:18:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也就没什么好说的了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.95,0:18:58.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.09,0:19:03.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没收到胡桃你的巧克力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.58,0:19:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.35,0:19:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是一个班的 还真是冷淡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.63,0:19:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过形象真是大转变了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.40,0:19:13.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前明明那么可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.50,0:19:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是更好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.26,0:19:17.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 以前比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.21,0:19:18.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好严厉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.43,0:19:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊 只要可爱是谁都无所谓吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.83,0:19:23.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子不都很可爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.15,0:19:25.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 也不是全部吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.30,0:19:38.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个是D班的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.77,0:19:39.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贞子？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.74,0:19:41.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就是传闻中的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.15,0:19:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种女生也会想要送巧克力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.46,0:19:55.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢礼什么的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.18,0:19:57.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是借口罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.37,0:20:04.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然并没有刻意的去期待什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.38,0:20:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我其实比想像中还要期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.00,0:20:16.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之所以害怕 是因为心存一点的期待
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.40,0:20:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是义理巧克力的话会收下的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.40,0:20:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那并不是人情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.17,0:20:24.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对 绝对不是人情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.78,0:20:27.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.86,0:20:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实是心存侥幸 希望能...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.55,0:20:37.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能更多和风早 和风早...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.42,0:20:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好像不收本命巧克力哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.62,0:20:52.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法送给他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.82,0:20:56.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想把这当做人情送给他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.07,0:20:59.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于这份感情太认真了 所以无法送给他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.64,0:21:01.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不后悔的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.62,0:21:08.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能送给他
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.98,0:21:13.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那份怀有私心的人情巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:26.80,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}どうか今だけは振り向かないで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.34,0:21:39.77,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}夕暮れさわぐ風　触れそうな距離
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.29,0:21:52.80,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君を見つめてる　ずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.28,0:21:59.06,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:05.71,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:11.53,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}叶わない恋でもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.67,0:22:14.85,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}傷ついてもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.01,0:22:19.74,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}何度でも伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.00,0:22:23.61,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君に届け
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:26.80,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}这一刻 请你不要回头看我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.34,0:21:39.77,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}在傍晚摇曳的风中 近在咫尺的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.29,0:21:52.80,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我一直 凝视着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.28,0:21:59.06,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.00,0:22:05.71,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}一直喜欢着你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:11.53,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使这份恋情永远也不能实现
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.67,0:22:14.85,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使会让我受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.01,0:22:19.74,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我也想一次又一次的让你感受到这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.00,0:22:23.61,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}好想告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.13,0:22:34.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\3c&H000007&\c&HF3F3F3&\pos(578,339)\fn汉仪丫丫体简}二年级生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.83,0:22:28.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,季节轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.25,0:22:30.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.73,0:22:34.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话 二年级生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:24:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H904F0D&\3c&HE1CFCA&\be3\fs20\pos(823,371)\fad(450,450)}异\N域\N字\N幕\N组\N长\N期\N招\N募\N翻\N译\N校\N译\N人\N员

