[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00f6eafe,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: endshengyoubiaoti,华康布丁体W12(P),32,&H00a074f4,&H000000ff,&H00e7cff9,&H004609cc,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFMaruGothic-Md,32,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,10,10,10,128
Style: edj,DFGMaruMoji-SL,33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00f7f7fa,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00c77638,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,微软雅黑,38,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,20,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,华康少女文字W5(P),33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(550,500)}异域字幕组作品\N{\be1\fad(0,500)}WWW.YYDM.COM
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}沐浴著溫暖的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}優しい日だまりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}鈴聲長長地響起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}チャイムがディレイする
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迎面輕撫而來的微風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}頬を撫でる風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}讓人情不自禁深深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}息吹は深くなっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迂迴的眼淚 注定的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}遠回りの涙　名前付けた明日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}宛如交織重疊的線條
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}重ねるみたい　いろんのライン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}年少天真無邪時的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}あどけない頃な気持ちも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}曾經燦爛歡笑的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}弾け飛ぶほど笑い会えた日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}我都小心翼翼留存在心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}大切に育ていているように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}穿越斷點的光陰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}途切れ途切れの時を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}帶給我許多從未體驗過的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}たくさんの初めてをくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}將你和我緊緊相連
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}繋がってゆけ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}届け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,327)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(350,400,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,238)}{\fs70}{\c&H74AFEB&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1150,1200,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,282)}{\fs70}{\c&HC080FF&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(750,800,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,194)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1550,1600,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,372)}{\fs70}{\c&H7CCFD3&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(50,100,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(530,360)}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}異\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}域\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}字\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}幕\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.91,0:01:04.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H303362&}第14話 胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.00,0:01:11.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謠言是指...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.31,0:01:14.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些矢野同學和吉田同學的壞話嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.82,0:01:16.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 沒錯沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.57,0:01:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有是我散佈謠言什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.96,0:01:21.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個也是那個也是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.37,0:01:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有我是幕後黑手什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.72,0:01:24.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幕後黑手?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.96,0:01:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像還有謠言說我把矢野同學和吉田同學當做靠山
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.91,0:01:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連風早同學都任我差遣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.86,0:01:34.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.26,0:01:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厲害 這樣不就能擺脫掉會詛咒人的謠言了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.91,0:01:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪惡 太邪惡了 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.54,0:01:50.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些傢伙 全都讓人很火大
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.84,0:01:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 應該是哪裡搞錯了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.62,0:01:57.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說就算是胡桃散佈這種謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.82,0:02:07.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在謠言世界中的我不但把你們當做靠山 還說你們的壞話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.01,0:02:09.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底想做什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.20,0:02:12.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是隨便編的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.66,0:02:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說 只是因為胡桃太笨了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.10,0:02:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 胡桃不笨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.00,0:02:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為總不做好事 所以很多事都聯繫不上 真是笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.51,0:02:27.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也太沒用了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:29.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 剛才在說什麼來著
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.72,0:02:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜傻瓜的 煩死了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.00,0:04:14.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,本片字幕由異域字幕組製作，僅供試看之用，請於試看後24小時內刪除。若因私自散佈造成法律問題，本組概不負責。如果喜歡本作品，請購買並支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.07,0:02:38.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法吧 散播謠言的不只我一個
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.85,0:02:44.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幕後黑手的謠言是風早迷們擅自捏造出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.30,0:02:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能全按計劃進行的話 我就不用這麼辛苦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.14,0:02:55.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃 不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.00,0:03:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 剛剛是有什麼地方誤會了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.09,0:03:05.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那個 如果好好說一定能說清楚的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.11,0:03:08.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為那種事 胡桃不會...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.83,0:03:09.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誤會?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.60,0:03:16.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是誤會
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.02,0:03:21.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說謊什麼的根本無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.52,0:03:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們兩人的壞話 還有始作俑者是爽子的這些謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.03,0:03:29.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散播的人 就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.12,0:21:04.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,翻譯 瑤瑤 阿虛 校譯時間 阿虛 後期 風一樣的人 義工 被風早同學萌倒的諾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.53,0:03:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是誤會
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.13,0:03:33.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 剛才她承認了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.60,0:03:38.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 在小千發覺之前更早一點的時候就已經承認了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.28,0:03:42.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.00,0:03:44.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你礙眼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.84,0:03:51.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很礙眼啊 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.75,0:03:57.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能和小千還有大家分開的話該有多好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.09,0:04:04.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃你...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.99,0:04:09.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.44,0:04:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.18,0:04:14.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才發現嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.02,0:04:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 我們是朋友了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.42,0:04:22.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.84,0:04:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從來沒有把你當成朋友看過
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.77,0:04:38.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真過分
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.89,0:04:41.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 她就是這種女人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.58,0:04:43.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快反駁她 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.41,0:04:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.71,0:04:57.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.10,0:05:00.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 你回 回話啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.96,0:05:05.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我忍無可忍了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.42,0:05:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 太不合我的性格了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.26,0:05:11.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就有話直說了 可以吧 矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.04,0:05:14.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.11,0:05:18.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經發生的事雖然生氣 但就那麼過去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.10,0:05:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不指望你能道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:23.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.63,0:05:26.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也就罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.43,0:05:30.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再隨便說些像是很瞭解矢野和爽子的話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.20,0:05:34.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 別再讓爽子哭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.70,0:05:39.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣 謠言的事就算解決了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.33,0:05:41.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輕鬆多了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.70,0:05:44.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又重新愛上你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.00,0:05:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後我也想要像小千一樣活著
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.84,0:05:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田同學
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.21,0:05:51.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有以後別利用別人了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.04,0:05:53.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.58,0:05:56.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說了 終於說了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.08,0:05:58.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然又變得很遜了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.06,0:06:09.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 你很狡猾啊 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.54,0:06:15.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用別人有什麼不好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.55,0:06:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家也一樣利用我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.42,0:06:19.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要了 就扔到一邊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.08,0:06:22.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我利用一下有什麼不對
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.17,0:06:26.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙的態度突然轉變了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.05,0:06:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說 你不打算改變自己的做法嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.51,0:06:36.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我一定要改變呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.34,0:06:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.06,0:06:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不像小千這麼老好人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.88,0:06:48.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 把這事告訴風早也不要緊嘍
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.89,0:06:54.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在馬上就去說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.60,0:06:55.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.57,0:06:56.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野同學
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.55,0:06:57.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說就說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.19,0:07:01.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說就說吧 對風早說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.25,0:07:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 我會說的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.24,0:07:09.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小千 接下來是排球比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.90,0:07:10.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.38,0:07:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 爽子也別理她了 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.15,0:07:23.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼還不走
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.17,0:07:27.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 把我的事告訴風早
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.39,0:07:34.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後再去換取風早的同情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.08,0:08:17.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 綾音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.30,0:08:21.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我小千呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.70,0:08:23.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才無意中就叫過了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.95,0:08:36.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事別說出去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.31,0:08:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說就說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.01,0:08:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不明白她為什麼會那麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.99,0:08:45.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種話絕對不是真心的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.02,0:08:48.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說就說吧 對風早說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.24,0:08:52.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不是真心的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.79,0:08:58.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你們別和風早同學說
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.24,0:09:03.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們本身對那就沒什麼興趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.64,0:09:06.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你說了 那就這麼辦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.52,0:09:07.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這樣好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.21,0:09:08.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.92,0:09:18.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為 誰都不想被喜歡的人討厭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.96,0:09:21.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.80,0:09:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.51,0:09:30.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒想到你會受那麼大的打擊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.07,0:09:34.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該說也不是完全沒有想到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.79,0:09:38.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是一不小心 摻雜了私人恩怨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.73,0:09:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼私人恩怨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.65,0:09:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綾音 這麼的為我著想
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.12,0:09:52.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也對不起你們
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.40,0:09:55.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你們也捲進來 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.19,0:09:56.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的 我們沒關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.83,0:09:59.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也沒有把謠言放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.87,0:10:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而是擔心你的謠言要不要緊才是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.61,0:10:08.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 已經習慣了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.90,0:10:10.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.10,0:10:18.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 謠言也不全是不好的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.87,0:10:31.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我交到了朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.13,0:10:52.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我的身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.26,0:10:57.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有小千和綾音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.97,0:11:03.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以能說出自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.15,0:11:18.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和胡桃又是什麼樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.27,0:11:24.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.23,0:11:28.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法嘛 那群傢伙是活力四射的排球社團嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.61,0:11:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.56,0:11:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 接著是足球
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.94,0:11:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃到底去哪裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.99,0:11:41.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 比賽也沒來 沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.55,0:11:44.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過也許胡桃不在才能贏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.18,0:11:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替補的真理子運動神經很不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.46,0:11:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃也不是很有幹勁的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.85,0:11:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像是「你再把頭髮紮緊一點」的那種感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.21,0:11:57.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.62,0:12:06.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃 在那之後沒有回去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.83,0:12:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有活力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.08,0:12:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑沼爽子同學吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.22,0:12:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.37,0:12:36.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.44,0:12:42.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.19,0:12:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊 小千
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.95,0:12:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.67,0:12:50.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫了我的本名
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.74,0:12:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說我們是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.95,0:12:59.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從來沒有把你當成朋友看過
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.18,0:13:04.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此 那時是她說我是她的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.39,0:13:07.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並且是胡桃先來和我說話的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.59,0:13:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是謊話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.50,0:13:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.22,0:13:21.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓我說出心裡話的 只有爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.65,0:13:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.55,0:13:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假的?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.96,0:13:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是真的?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.25,0:13:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多謝指教
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.38,0:13:50.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 Yeah
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.13,0:13:59.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有話要對胡桃說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.68,0:14:00.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？胡桃？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.40,0:14:02.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.06,0:14:09.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛爽子什麼都沒對胡桃說
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.86,0:14:14.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似只有我們兩個說個不停
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.44,0:14:19.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然交情還不深
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.83,0:14:23.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有很多不瞭解的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.18,0:14:26.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.94,0:14:33.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃把她最珍貴的感情告訴了我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.15,0:14:37.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想告訴胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.11,0:14:39.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.30,0:14:43.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我最珍視的這份感情告訴她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.48,0:14:51.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 難道女生足球已經結束了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.63,0:14:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.75,0:14:54.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 現在才來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.49,0:14:58.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是 小痞說什麼也不放我走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.41,0:15:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是體育祭委員嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.38,0:15:05.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 帥哥真是辛苦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.87,0:15:10.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們看啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.71,0:15:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 這裡是不是吐槽一下比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.77,0:15:16.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吐哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.46,0:15:19.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道你們也?放棄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.90,0:15:22.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.23,0:15:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子去找胡桃了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.15,0:15:27.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃澤?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.24,0:15:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那個女生嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.15,0:15:32.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是哪個
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.16,0:15:35.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個就是那個
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.64,0:15:39.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是個罪惡深重的男人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.53,0:15:47.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個女生 肯定在什麼地方悲傷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.75,0:15:53.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一邊思念著我 一邊悲傷
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.53,0:16:02.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我又讓一個女人不幸了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.46,0:16:07.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你們絕對不要像那個女生一樣迷上我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.82,0:16:09.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對小P孩沒有興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.57,0:16:12.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小痞 別到處亂說 她多可憐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.08,0:16:19.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對著有著與生俱來的纖細敏感的神經的我 你說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.34,0:16:18.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.49,0:16:20.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃的品味好差
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.66,0:16:22.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會選上小痞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.29,0:16:23.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.89,0:16:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次覺得胡桃好可憐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.26,0:16:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我都同情她了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.47,0:16:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.58,0:17:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來做什麼 是想要嘲笑我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.82,0:17:05.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是來說剛剛忘記說的抱怨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.18,0:17:07.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕快說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.03,0:17:10.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者說 難道是來同情我的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.74,0:17:16.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.77,0:17:25.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用真正的戀愛感情強烈地喜歡上了風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.60,0:17:33.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛就是為了說這個而來的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.43,0:17:37.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要告訴胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.06,0:17:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次說出口
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.30,0:17:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把這件事告訴朋友真的很讓人激動
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.41,0:17:56.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳好快
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.99,0:18:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加速的心跳讓自己真正體會到自己是喜歡風早同學的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.74,0:18:10.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來告訴我的時候胡桃是這樣的心情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.63,0:18:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是說過我們不是朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.90,0:18:18.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以別把我和你相提並論
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.15,0:18:20.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒有覺得緊張嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.21,0:18:24.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有覺得有一點害羞嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.01,0:18:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有覺得有一點開心嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.13,0:18:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用語言表達的時候 發覺自己喜歡他的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.42,0:18:44.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開心?為什麼我要因為告訴了爽子而開心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.02,0:18:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是說過你很礙眼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.06,0:18:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭可以輕易的留在風早身邊的你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.03,0:18:58.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得如果對手是爽子的話 我能贏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.00,0:19:06.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我比爽子要更加 更加...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.14,0:19:11.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 比起我來 胡桃和風早更加相配
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.63,0:19:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加喜歡風早
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.80,0:19:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.93,0:19:24.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是這樣的喜歡風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.24,0:19:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡桃非常非常的喜歡風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.05,0:19:44.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起原來的胡桃 我覺得現在的胡桃要更加更加的可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.61,0:19:47.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你知道我可愛...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.63,0:19:52.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有什麼意義
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.11,0:19:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果風早不喜歡我 又有什麼意義
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.88,0:20:05.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 知道風早並不喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.90,0:20:09.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我一直都在注視著他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.61,0:20:13.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要回來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.08,0:20:19.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你的面前 哭成這樣...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.95,0:20:28.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為胡桃知道風早同學所有的優點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.20,0:20:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以這些事 是和胡桃的話就可以相互交流
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.11,0:20:46.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最討厭你了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.22,0:20:56.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之所以羨慕胡桃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.29,0:21:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定並不只是因為長相 氣質 或者她和風早同學更相配
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.96,0:21:13.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是因為喜歡上風早同學的胡桃非常可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.03,0:21:26.02,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.03,0:21:26.02,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.98,0:21:36.34,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いかない　それが答えてなんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.98,0:21:36.34,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 那就是回答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.59,0:21:39.75,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シャボン玉　飛ばそう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.59,0:21:39.75,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡泡 飄飄浮浮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.28,0:21:48.03,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空まではきっと届かない　うちに壊れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.28,0:21:48.03,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還未到達天空就破滅消散而去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.39,0:21:53.56,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま誰知りたいの永遠じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.39,0:21:53.56,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們想要的永遠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.82,0:22:01.22,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままずっと　いていたいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.82,0:22:01.22,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管想要永遠留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.58,0:22:12.49,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.58,0:22:12.49,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.30,0:22:22.03,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.30,0:22:22.03,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只找尋到了屬於我的唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.86,0:22:34.71,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(632,361)}第15話 競爭對手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.84,0:22:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絲毫不帶偏見的注視著我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.84,0:22:30.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使現在也一直是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.24,0:22:33.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一話 競爭對手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.66,0:22:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家期待已久的好想告訴你 漫畫第十卷將在1月13日發售
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.30,0:22:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我們就請穿著爽子連衣裙的編輯池田小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.58,0:22:52.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我們一下本次的看點
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.82,0:22:55.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在第十卷中爽子終於
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.78,0:22:56.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子終於
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.79,0:22:57.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和風早
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.69,0:22:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和風早
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.68,0:22:59.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[嗶——]
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.67,0:23:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[嗶——]嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.98,0:23:08.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要知道的觀眾請去看1月13日發售的別冊瑪格麗特2月號
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.15,0:23:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很讓人在意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.11,0:23:15.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且2月號中附帶有作為贈品的好想告訴你信紙套裝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.42,0:23:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼來周再見 告訴你
