[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00f6eafe,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: endshengyoubiaoti,华康布丁体W12(P),32,&H00a074f4,&H000000ff,&H00e7cff9,&H004609cc,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFMaruGothic-Md,32,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,10,10,10,128
Style: edj,DFGMaruMoji-SL,33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00f7f7fa,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00c77638,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,微软雅黑,38,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,20,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,华康少女文字W5(P),33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(550,500)}异域字幕组作品\N{\be1\fad(0,500)}WWW.YYDM.COM
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}沐浴著溫暖的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}優しい日だまりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}鈴聲長長地響起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}チャイムがディレイする
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迎面輕撫而來的微風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}頬を撫でる風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}讓人情不自禁深深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}息吹は深くなっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迂迴的眼淚 注定的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}遠回りの涙　名前付けた明日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}宛如交織重疊的線條
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}重ねるみたい　いろんのライン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}年少天真無邪時的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}あどけない頃な気持ちも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}曾經燦爛歡笑的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}弾け飛ぶほど笑い会えた日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}我都小心翼翼留存在心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}大切に育ていているように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}穿越斷點的光陰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}途切れ途切れの時を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}帶給我許多從未體驗過的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}たくさんの初めてをくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}將你和我緊緊相連
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}繋がってゆけ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}届け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,327)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(350,400,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,238)}{\fs70}{\c&H74AFEB&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1150,1200,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,282)}{\fs70}{\c&HC080FF&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(750,800,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,194)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1550,1600,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,372)}{\fs70}{\c&H7CCFD3&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(50,100,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(530,360)}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}異\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}域\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}字\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}幕\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}組
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.53,0:01:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你見到胡桃的時候不是想過要變得可愛嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.90,0:01:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼想要變可愛 自己好好想想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.39,0:01:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快樂 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.07,0:01:55.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍還沒來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.58,0:01:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田和矢野呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.30,0:02:01.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.58,0:02:07.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真田同學他也不來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.35,0:02:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.76,0:02:37.75,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HDEC5C0&}第24話 生日
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.00,0:04:14.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,本片字幕由異域字幕組製作，僅供試看之用，請於試看後24小時內刪除。若因私自散佈造成法律問題，本組概不負責。如果喜歡本作品，請購買並支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.99,0:03:07.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不看我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.97,0:03:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.04,0:03:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像也無法注視著他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.12,0:21:04.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,人員表 翻譯 瑤瑤 老虎 校譯 時間 阿虛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.41,0:03:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危險
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.32,0:03:57.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腳下 台階...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.59,0:03:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.94,0:04:02.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 台階 我好像沒看到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.72,0:04:04.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所 所以 那...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.86,0:04:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 他們怎麼什麼都沒做
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.34,0:04:14.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是急死人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.49,0:04:16.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 打電話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.35,0:04:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.62,0:04:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把碰頭的地方改在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.16,0:04:22.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們到底要幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.32,0:04:23.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噓 別說話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.47,0:04:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早啊 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.66,0:04:37.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田 你在哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.66,0:04:39.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.39,0:04:41.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聲音太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.50,0:04:43.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.12,0:04:48.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 突然不能去了真不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.25,0:04:51.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍他也突然有事要忙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.61,0:04:54.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我跟風早你說聲抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.21,0:04:59.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就替我們多許幾個願望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.00,0:05:02.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.70,0:05:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛是幻覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.52,0:05:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然不能去的事我也跟爽子說過了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.56,0:05:14.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可能會不知所措
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.37,0:05:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正 一切都交給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.30,0:05:20.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.36,0:05:22.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.96,0:05:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田打來的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.17,0:05:29.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說突然不能來了真抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.86,0:05:35.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來 我都沒有好好解釋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.46,0:05:39.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 她們在幫我解釋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.99,0:05:45.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不冷嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.27,0:05:50.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離12點還有一段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.36,0:05:54.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對面在發甜酒 我們過去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.36,0:05:59.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.09,0:06:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在我的身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.88,0:06:36.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於對話了 還並肩散步啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.07,0:06:39.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來要去喝甜酒啊 喝甜酒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.01,0:06:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們先潛伏過去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.90,0:06:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們的趣味真是惡劣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.28,0:06:48.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還和翔太說過今天的計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.16,0:06:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越來越有趣了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.03,0:06:54.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遠遠不夠 現在開始才是重頭戲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.16,0:06:57.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無所謂了 我想喝甜酒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.38,0:07:02.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火真旺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.49,0:07:04.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白癡到處都有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.62,0:07:07.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說 那不是城麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.59,0:07:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.32,0:07:13.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班級的恥辱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.15,0:07:15.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.04,0:07:18.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說和他父母長的好像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.00,0:07:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜酒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.50,0:07:23.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 爽子和風早...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.79,0:07:27.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話剛好走到城的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.46,0:07:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 那傢伙超級萌風早 肯定會纏著他們的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.29,0:07:33.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.21,0:07:34.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.86,0:07:35.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的甜酒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.82,0:07:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點 龍
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.90,0:07:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好暖和啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.32,0:07:52.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是城嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.18,0:07:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城 真是巧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.13,0:07:58.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事 你們幾個一起來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.11,0:08:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍 你也叫我嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.21,0:08:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城你和誰來的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.40,0:08:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸媽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.31,0:08:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平時的那一幫人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.78,0:08:09.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家看搞笑節目呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.31,0:08:12.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 礙事的只來了一個
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.36,0:08:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 風早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:21.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛才一瞬好像看到風早了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.20,0:08:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早 風早說他不來的 你看錯了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.02,0:08:28.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.07,0:08:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煩人 都說是了 來的話肯定在這吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.68,0:08:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她挽著我的胳膊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.84,0:08:40.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是 而且好像還和美女一起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.82,0:08:44.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好這傢伙是個白癡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.08,0:08:48.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野她沒準喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.68,0:08:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想喝甜酒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.43,0:08:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.51,0:08:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了就好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 搞不好碰到胸了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.00,0:09:04.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不會讓你碰到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.61,0:09:14.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小火星
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.21,0:09:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然大家聚到一起 我們就去喝喝甜酒聊聊天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.10,0:09:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最討厭甜酒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.73,0:09:26.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜酒禁止
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.09,0:09:28.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.12,0:09:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜酒呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.65,0:09:39.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熱乎乎的甜酒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.69,0:09:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一杯嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.46,0:09:44.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一杯甜酒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.63,0:09:48.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡有甜酒 請喝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.19,0:09:51.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一杯嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.73,0:09:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好喝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.64,0:09:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請給我們兩杯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.44,0:09:58.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 小情侶兩杯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.95,0:10:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小情侶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.51,0:10:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.72,0:10:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.74,0:10:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.27,0:10:20.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到我聽了這麼開心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.29,0:10:26.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不害臊 明明是誤會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.13,0:10:29.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早同學會不會覺得討厭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.91,0:10:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定會討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.80,0:10:35.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真暖和啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.58,0:10:42.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許只有我一個人在意 好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.28,0:10:48.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.53,0:10:49.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.55,0:11:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出生以來頭一回覺得甜酒好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.12,0:11:06.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本來討厭喝甜酒的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.53,0:11:09.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 要說的話 是不太能喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.69,0:11:12.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.81,0:11:16.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好開心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.70,0:11:18.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直很想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.51,0:11:20.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從沒見過的風早同學的一面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.26,0:11:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次聽到風早同學說「出生以來第一次」的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.18,0:11:33.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看到大家都不瞭解的風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.51,0:11:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種東西你不是已經見過了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.94,0:11:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣兩個人單獨去神社也是出生以來的第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.77,0:11:55.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便說一句 買女生用的手機鏈也是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.16,0:11:58.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有一個
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.45,0:12:05.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿腹帶今天也是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.12,0:12:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口袋裡放了暖袋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.68,0:12:13.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧這個肚子好暖和的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.27,0:12:16.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 但那是爸爸...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.36,0:12:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 別說了 這已經是我的東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.73,0:12:29.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然我還是想送帽子給風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.74,0:12:33.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對 就算不是帽子也好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.41,0:12:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為風早同學做的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.57,0:12:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為風早同學選的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.67,0:12:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直希望他能收下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.96,0:12:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許他會收下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.82,0:12:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許他會使用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.06,0:13:00.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼 郵件地址定好了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.82,0:13:03.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.14,0:13:05.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以發郵件給你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.52,0:13:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現 現在就發
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.18,0:13:10.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不過是第一次發
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.14,0:13:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能會用很長時間
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.12,0:13:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 慢慢來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.54,0:13:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想對風早同學說的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.40,0:13:36.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要告訴風早同學的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.86,0:13:40.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 打錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.81,0:13:42.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的想一下的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.25,0:13:45.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要告訴他的事太多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.03,0:13:49.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而不知道該從何說起了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.74,0:13:57.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果用一句話就能表達自己的感情就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.90,0:14:07.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發送
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.02,0:14:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電話號碼...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.51,0:14:14.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有點後悔那個時候沒有問你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.02,0:14:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能不是有一點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.20,0:14:23.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是強行問出來也比不問要好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.71,0:14:27.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 收到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.89,0:14:35.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(今年真是非常感謝你)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.48,0:14:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(謝謝你今天陪我的身邊 我非常開心)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.95,0:14:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(爽子.not.貞子.1231)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.33,0:14:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到3又回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.84,0:14:55.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的生日是哪一天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.79,0:15:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.53,0:15:25.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有15分鐘不就結束了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.88,0:15:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.28,0:15:31.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 勉勉強強趕上了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.95,0:15:40.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.01,0:15:44.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果早點知道的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.67,0:15:46.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能送你點禮物了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.46,0:15:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經收到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.72,0:16:03.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了原本不知道的風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.62,0:16:07.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了風早同學的第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.66,0:16:14.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 我差不多就是出生在這個時間
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.11,0:16:18.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在變成16歲的瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.20,0:16:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你和我在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.00,0:16:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,23點45分
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.34,0:16:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,16歲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.73,0:16:34.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距離新年來臨還有15分鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.15,0:16:43.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼以前是個什麼樣的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.24,0:16:49.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 應該說是個很普通的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.63,0:16:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 該怎麼說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.01,0:16:54.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就按順序來說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.91,0:16:58.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,16年前的今天出生之後呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.78,0:17:00.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會很無聊的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.97,0:17:02.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係哦 無聊也沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.91,0:17:04.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.65,0:17:07.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.72,0:17:11.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的會很無聊的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.07,0:17:15.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,16年前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.83,0:17:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出生重3kg
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.71,0:17:21.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4歲進入幼兒園
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.02,0:17:24.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分別是菫和鈴蘭班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.89,0:17:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 就是那個時候表哥開始叫我「座敷童子」的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.14,0:17:34.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,座敷童子　我想喝可樂　座敷童子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.18,0:17:36.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.79,0:17:39.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事好像還到處跟別人炫耀去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.20,0:17:44.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小學1 2年紀的時候是梅班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.63,0:17:46.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3　4年紀的時候呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.89,0:17:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是松班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.15,0:17:49.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5　6年級呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.41,0:17:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竹班
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.07,0:17:52.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松竹梅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.25,0:17:54.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候的興趣是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.38,0:17:56.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,興趣?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.61,0:17:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,興趣...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.72,0:18:02.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是一個人跳橡皮筋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.76,0:18:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人跳橡皮筋?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.18,0:18:06.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把繩子繫在兩把椅子上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.86,0:18:08.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後跳繩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.32,0:18:12.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時是很流行的 在我看來...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.80,0:18:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有就是一個人玩排球
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.07,0:18:17.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人玩翻繩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.54,0:18:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 七層台階
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.88,0:18:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人玩牌
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.29,0:18:22.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 速度好快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.35,0:18:24.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.41,0:18:28.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 很晦暗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.54,0:18:32.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然可能會冷場
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.63,0:18:35.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是大過年的...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.84,0:18:35.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有那樣的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.14,0:18:39.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 入學的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.03,0:18:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果聽到剛剛你這番話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.80,0:18:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或許會覺得你喜歡自己一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.44,0:18:47.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是自從開始和你聊天以來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.07,0:18:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你身邊看了那麼久
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.67,0:18:52.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發現黑沼不管做什麼都很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.99,0:18:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我覺得你很擅長找到開心的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.28,0:19:00.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能夠這樣想像 我就覺得很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.08,0:19:06.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來他一直是這樣看待我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.35,0:19:08.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.18,0:19:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12歲進入初中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.50,0:19:16.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 小學已經結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.24,0:19:19.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平平淡淡度過了這一段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.25,0:19:26.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3年級的時候決定考離家最近的北幌高中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.84,0:19:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15歲的春天
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.54,0:19:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.66,0:19:42.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能成為像風早同學一樣的人的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.65,0:19:47.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也會...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.72,0:19:50.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些變化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.04,0:19:58.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.56,0:20:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,契機一直都是風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.49,0:20:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年一整年
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.84,0:20:32.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和以前的時間差別太大
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.12,0:20:37.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來會變得很長很長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.54,0:20:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和風早同學一起度過這一年
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.46,0:21:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起過的生日就要結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.84,0:21:10.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的一年即將開始
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いかない　それが答えてなんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 那就是回答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シャボン玉　飛ばそう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡泡 飄飄浮浮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空まではきっと届かない　うちに壊れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還未到達天空就破滅消散而去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま誰知りたいの永遠じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們想要的永遠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままずっと　いていたいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管想要永遠留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只找尋到了屬於我的唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.02,0:22:34.83,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(681,364)}第25話 新年
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.14,0:22:32.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一話 新年
