[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00f6eafe,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFMaruGothic-Md,32,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,10,10,10,128
Style: endshengyoubiaoti,华康布丁体W12(P),32,&H00a074f4,&H000000ff,&H00e7cff9,&H004609cc,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edj,DFGMaruMoji-SL,33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00f7f7fa,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00c77638,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,微软雅黑,38,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,20,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,华康少女文字W5(P),33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(550,500)}异域字幕组作品\N{\be1\fad(0,500)}WWW.YYDM.COM
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}沐浴著溫暖的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}優しい日だまりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}鈴聲長長地響起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}チャイムがディレイする
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迎面輕撫而來的微風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}頬を撫でる風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}讓人情不自禁深深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}息吹は深くなっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迂迴的眼淚 注定的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}遠回りの涙　名前付けた明日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}宛如交織重疊的線條
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}重ねるみたい　いろんのライン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}年少天真無邪時的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}あどけない頃な気持ちも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}曾經燦爛歡笑的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}弾け飛ぶほど笑い会えた日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}我都小心翼翼留存在心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}大切に育ていているように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}穿越斷點的光陰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}途切れ途切れの時を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}帶給我許多從未體驗過的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}たくさんの初めてをくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}將你和我緊緊相連
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}繋がってゆけ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}届け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,327)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(350,400,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,238)}{\fs70}{\c&H74AFEB&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1150,1200,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,282)}{\fs70}{\c&HC080FF&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(750,800,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,194)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1550,1600,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,372)}{\fs70}{\c&H7CCFD3&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(50,100,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(530,360)}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}異\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}域\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}字\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}幕\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}組
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.36,0:01:05.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 我出發了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.62,0:01:11.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩的開心點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.97,0:01:16.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子第一次去朋友家過夜 爸爸我...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.67,0:01:19.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該做什麼好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.70,0:01:22.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子他爸什麼都不用做
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.67,0:01:29.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 爸爸會打電話過去的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.62,0:01:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和對方的父母打個招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.22,0:01:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得把當做禮物的羊羹拿出來哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.01,0:01:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.26,0:01:42.21,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HDCE7FB&\3c&H8BA5D1&}第19話 夢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.42,0:01:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是我有生以來第一次去朋友家過夜的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.97,0:01:55.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和綾音一起 去小千家裡過夜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.87,0:02:01.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千鶴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.71,0:02:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.41,0:02:11.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.97,0:02:13.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早晨好 小千
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.05,0:02:15.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早晨好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.79,0:02:18.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早晨好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.37,0:02:22.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥啊 過夜套裝?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.00,0:02:23.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.44,0:02:25.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說啥來著
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.62,0:02:28.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.70,0:02:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相對的 明天和後天絕對不要來我家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.20,0:04:14.62,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,本片字幕由異域字幕組製作，僅供試看之用，請於試看後24小時內刪除。若因私自散佈造成法律問題，本組概不負責。如果喜歡本作品，請購買並支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.39,0:02:36.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.50,0:02:38.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等...為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.92,0:02:41.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.49,0:02:44.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 你惹龍生氣了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.36,0:02:49.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 可惡的龍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.40,0:02:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家還想好好的玩一場遊戲 讓矢野打起精神來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.59,0:02:58.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玩遊戲不就行了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.64,0:03:01.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為遊戲都是龍的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.83,0:03:04.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還想著要去龍家呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.62,0:03:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你啊 不知道自己做了什麼惹他生氣的事情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.31,0:03:10.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 沒有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.07,0:03:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是上次他來的時候 我很堅決的把他趕走了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.63,0:03:16.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.69,0:03:19.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這個差點被看到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.47,0:03:19.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(621,413)}(送給龍)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.89,0:03:24.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為這個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.01,0:03:27.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點事情算什麼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.25,0:03:28.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心眼太小了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.32,0:21:04.62,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,人員表 翻譯 阿虛 老虎 時間 校譯 阿虛 義工 被風早同學萌倒的諾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.61,0:03:30.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都怪到別人頭上了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.12,0:03:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天和後天 絕對不要來我家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.92,0:03:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 明天明明是龍的生日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.73,0:03:45.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(412,375)}(垃圾桶)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.97,0:03:45.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種東西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.72,0:03:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是下不了手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.94,0:03:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 到龍家去玩遊戲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.32,0:03:57.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他又沒說今天不准去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.94,0:03:59.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便和他和好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日禮物也一起帶去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.39,0:04:06.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是因為這個惹他生氣 那不就沒有意義了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.62,0:04:13.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野 我愛死你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.90,0:04:14.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖 乖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.98,0:04:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.78,0:04:23.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常讓人意外的不防守戰術
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.77,0:04:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戀愛的絕地反擊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.97,0:04:29.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很強大吧 今天很強大吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.58,0:04:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 所以一直沒說出口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.60,0:04:37.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是找不到時機
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.38,0:04:39.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.73,0:04:43.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只要像往常一樣在正月見到哥哥就好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.98,0:04:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒必要特意安排千鶴和哥哥見面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.49,0:04:55.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這麼多人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.27,0:04:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們來幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.61,0:05:00.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們才是 來這裡做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.22,0:05:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們正在舉行城的安慰大會
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.31,0:05:04.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.55,0:05:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的失戀同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.85,0:05:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是正好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.42,0:05:11.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城和矢野的共同安慰大會
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.12,0:05:14.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.94,0:05:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.48,0:05:20.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常有這種事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.36,0:05:23.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失戀的二人在相互安慰的過程中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.24,0:05:25.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,產生了愛情的萌芽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.15,0:05:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是矢野嗎...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.66,0:05:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的要尊敬城了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.59,0:05:30.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.54,0:05:35.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天沒關係吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.88,0:05:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.08,0:05:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你們幾個擠一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.02,0:05:43.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.48,0:05:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.24,0:05:54.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有誰能說點有趣的話題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.61,0:05:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.91,0:05:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.92,0:05:57.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然沒有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.53,0:05:59.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.93,0:06:02.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野 矢野為什麼分了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.17,0:06:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多原因啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.38,0:06:06.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺有點不可思議
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.45,0:06:07.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我點什麼喝的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.31,0:06:09.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在朋友的家裡過夜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.80,0:06:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待在這麼多人的中間
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.87,0:06:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽聽別人的戀愛故事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.81,0:06:20.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 說起來 上次的事情...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.95,0:06:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然見到自己喜歡的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.40,0:06:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一切 全部...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.49,0:06:27.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在都已經不再是和我無關的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.99,0:06:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍 給我個杯子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.41,0:06:35.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡的拉麵可強大了 *&*%$#@...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.81,0:06:34.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.75,0:06:42.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.74,0:06:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便把這個給他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.10,0:06:49.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他能高興就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.45,0:06:51.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野 喜歡什麼類型的男生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.04,0:06:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸懷寬廣 處變不驚的成熟男人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.58,0:07:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.10,0:07:05.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在生氣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.49,0:07:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.71,0:07:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.99,0:07:14.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說沒在生氣...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.68,0:07:18.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是被人像那樣趕出家門
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.72,0:07:20.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也會有點受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.08,0:07:25.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.99,0:07:28.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並不是因為龍做錯了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.94,0:07:32.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我想把開心的事情留到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.68,0:07:40.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想告訴我什麼事情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.06,0:07:44.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.66,0:07:47.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.58,0:07:49.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.87,0:07:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.75,0:08:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累死了 累死了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.89,0:08:03.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.17,0:08:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.27,0:08:15.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.21,0:08:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.78,0:08:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼有力氣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.48,0:08:26.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 你長大了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.67,0:08:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 我沒聽說你要回來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.06,0:08:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.52,0:08:33.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本沒覺得抱歉嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.06,0:08:39.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是說明天回來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.01,0:08:42.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因為今天工作提前結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.46,0:08:45.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非那個就是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.85,0:08:46.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.61,0:08:51.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.74,0:08:52.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 翔太啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.95,0:08:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭髮這麼長了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.64,0:09:00.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 風早 現在是我在和徹說話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.80,0:09:04.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人就是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.95,0:09:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千喜歡的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.71,0:09:08.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有女孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.02,0:09:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一手嘛 龍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.98,0:09:12.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是千鶴的朋友...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.32,0:09:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中裡的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.29,0:09:16.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字是爽子和矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.88,0:09:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來 過來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.36,0:09:21.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不討厭這種類型呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.09,0:09:23.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把矢野藏起來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.25,0:09:25.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞進壁櫥裡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.47,0:09:26.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開玩笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.04,0:09:30.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千一點都沒變啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.41,0:09:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然 只穿著睡衣和牛仔褲就來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.43,0:09:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs18\pos(590,155)\frz356.395}(穿著這個直接就睡覺)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.15,0:09:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs18\frz350.77\pos(544,259)}(只是換了下褲子)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.70,0:09:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不是新的也應該穿條超短裙來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.45,0:09:44.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說龍 為什麼沒告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.86,0:09:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 快進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.16,0:09:54.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係嗎 我可以進去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:56.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.20,0:09:59.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行李只有這些嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.54,0:10:00.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的全部拿出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.20,0:10:13.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.80,0:10:16.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.20,0:10:20.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...是女朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.67,0:10:25.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我們要結婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.72,0:10:26.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次見面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.33,0:10:29.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.77,0:10:31.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.14,0:10:41.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 振作點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.78,0:10:44.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這小子就是我弟弟 龍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.40,0:10:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小千
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.18,0:10:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是徹的弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.95,0:10:48.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫做片山遙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.82,0:10:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 這孩子也介紹下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.88,0:10:57.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田千鶴 叫她小千就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.67,0:11:01.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從小時候開始就像妹妹一樣疼愛她
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.32,0:11:09.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是片山 請多多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.37,0:11:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.33,0:11:19.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是他們的鄰居 叫做吉田
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.74,0:11:27.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既不是家人也不是親戚 總覺得...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.58,0:11:29.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.55,0:11:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是 請多關照
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.72,0:11:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 別說得那麼見外嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.95,0:11:41.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結婚算啥...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.37,0:11:42.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.42,0:11:45.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.43,0:11:48.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就散了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.78,0:11:52.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得徹哥哥回來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.36,0:11:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田你們也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.21,0:11:56.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我們就一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.31,0:11:59.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.80,0:12:03.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似來的時機很糟糕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.68,0:12:09.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊的無關人士們 趕快回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.82,0:12:12.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這個主角就這麼退場了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.27,0:12:15.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說你也是無關人士吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.62,0:12:17.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才和大家一起回家嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.24,0:12:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了 再見*6
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.15,0:12:26.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.74,0:12:33.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 路上小心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.56,0:12:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也沒變嘛 我家很近嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.45,0:12:40.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也很強嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.40,0:12:42.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.51,0:12:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.19,0:12:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的你想些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.19,0:13:02.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.48,0:13:04.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太 你覺得怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.81,0:13:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我在那個場合下說點什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.61,0:13:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得千鶴會因為我擔心她而感到沮喪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.88,0:13:18.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生氣的話還好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.39,0:13:23.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在一定很沮喪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.96,0:13:30.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼說 龍一直都在擔心吉田
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.65,0:13:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是龍的錯 別太失落了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.01,0:13:38.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是沒在失落呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.41,0:13:50.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白 我是不是真的擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.50,0:13:53.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.63,0:13:59.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很喜歡呢 吉田
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.76,0:14:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕 又是我一個人贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.65,0:14:15.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之後連續打了4小時的牌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.03,0:14:16.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來做什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.22,0:14:19.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.48,0:14:21.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.16,0:14:26.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.42,0:14:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指徹的事情麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.18,0:14:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來我還沒有恭喜他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.42,0:14:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天去見下徹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.58,0:14:50.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得自己一直憧憬的哥哥就要結婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.31,0:14:56.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 會有更好的男人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.55,0:15:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.64,0:15:05.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 總覺得不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.42,0:15:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得你們兩個要提前回去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.25,0:15:10.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得是矢野的安慰會
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.94,0:15:14.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 那個已經完全忘記了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.72,0:15:17.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 已經這個時間了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.98,0:15:19.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多該睡了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.61,0:15:38.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我單相思的時間可是很長的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.70,0:15:43.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他現在還不會注視著我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.41,0:15:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要成為一個好女人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.33,0:15:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等長大之後 就不一定了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.45,0:15:57.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡的是龍的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.32,0:16:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 已經起來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.32,0:16:31.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 吵醒你了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.55,0:16:36.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要穿迷你裙哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.71,0:16:41.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 或許不是已經起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.46,0:16:45.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是睡不著吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.88,0:16:47.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯吧 這件運動衫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.06,0:16:49.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥穿剩下來的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.50,0:16:52.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然這裡有個洞 但完全沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.79,0:16:57.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.33,0:17:09.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見 到學校再見哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.20,0:17:26.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為她會像以前一樣哇哇大哭 然後對我們發牢騷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.11,0:17:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始還搞不清楚她是不是覺得難過...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.97,0:17:38.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.55,0:17:43.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有什麼我們能做的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.44,0:17:48.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 現在的狀況啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.10,0:17:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能問她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.86,0:17:54.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是結果還是沒有我們能做的...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.24,0:17:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說是要穿迷你裙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.23,0:18:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是那麼的開心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.83,0:18:09.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是安慰還是鼓勵
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.41,0:18:12.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都沒有做到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.79,0:18:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼話都沒說
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.99,0:18:20.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都沒對小千說...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.90,0:18:31.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.25,0:18:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏偏是在這種時候 說不出一句有用的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.53,0:18:42.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所謂朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.56,0:18:47.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這種時候該怎麼做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.63,0:18:57.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔笑的真開心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.19,0:19:05.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說像女兒一樣又不是女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.53,0:19:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說像妹妹一樣又不是妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.13,0:19:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的既不是親戚也不是什麼別的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.41,0:19:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這重要的閤家歡樂的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.75,0:19:17.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄰居家的孩子摻和進去算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.05,0:19:23.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄰居家的孩子麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.11,0:19:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍 來比賽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.65,0:19:35.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs18\pos(373,389)}龍 千鶴 小學三年級
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.74,0:19:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不動真格的話就殺了你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.32,0:19:39.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.31,0:19:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍 不能弄哭女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.95,0:19:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\pos(628,396)}徹 高二
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.63,0:19:51.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛的痛痛的飛走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.05,0:19:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹 我抓到蟲子了 快來看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.56,0:20:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹 蟲子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.26,0:20:06.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹 蟲子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.44,0:20:10.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼是蟲子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.19,0:20:14.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候的愛情表現 真不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.72,0:20:16.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.40,0:20:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊 小千
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.02,0:20:24.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他總是會對我微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.35,0:20:30.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹他身邊的經常有女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.06,0:20:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是每個交往的時間都不長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.46,0:20:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想 就算交往也不過如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.94,0:20:42.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我的夢想就是成為他的...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.51,0:20:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹的新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.22,0:21:03.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實現我的夢想的人...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.54,0:21:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いかない　それが答えてなんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 那就是回答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シャボン玉　飛ばそう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡泡 飄飄浮浮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空まではきっと届かない　うちに壊れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還未到達天空就破滅消散而去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま誰知りたいの永遠じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們想要的永遠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままずっと　いていたいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管想要永遠留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只找尋到了屬於我的唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.85,0:22:34.36,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(684,363)}第20話 禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.81,0:22:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無法傳達的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.71,0:22:30.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奪眶而出的淚水
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.36,0:22:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一話 禮物
