[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00fffff1,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFGPOP1-W9,24,&H00fffff1,&H000000ff,&H00e7a65c,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,128
Style: edj,DFGPOP1-W9,22,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00d5a39e,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H0048103e,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,时尚中黑简体,27,&H00fffff1,&H000000ff,&H00e7a65c,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,18,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,时尚中黑简体,26,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00d5a39e,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.54,0:00:05.24,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}まっしろ　ページめくる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.54,0:00:05.24,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}翻過這純白的一頁
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.89,0:00:13.43,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}飛び出す色と弾ける万華鏡の風景
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.89,0:00:13.43,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}映入眼睛的是萬花筒一般絢麗的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.07,0:00:15.41,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}気づけば
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.07,0:00:15.41,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}等我發覺的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.32,0:00:18.85,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ストーリーはまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.32,0:00:18.85,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我們的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:23.67,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}ぎこちなく　始まったばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:23.67,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}才剛剛的開始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.74,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}深呼吸をもう一回
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:26.74,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}再深呼吸一次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.89,0:00:33.69,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}旅する風　包み込むように背中を押す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.89,0:00:33.69,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}風像是催促著我踏上旅途一樣 推著我前行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.84,0:00:41.85,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}あ　柔らかくて　暖かい君の手　握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.84,0:00:41.85,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}啊 我握住你那柔軟而溫暖的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:47.02,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}その心の奥まで届くように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.01,0:00:47.02,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}希望我的心情能夠傳遞到你的心裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.17,0:00:50.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}微笑んでくれたなら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.17,0:00:50.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你用微笑回應我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.41,0:00:54.44,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}握り返してくれたら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.41,0:00:54.44,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}如果你也握緊我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.58,0:00:58.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}僕はただ前を見てる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.58,0:00:58.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}那麼 我只需要一路前行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.07,0:01:05.04,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be2\blur1\3c&HE7BB9A&\c&H834131&}第五話 喜歡的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.80,0:01:10.80,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}本片字幕由異域字幕組(www.yydm.com)製作,僅供試看之用,如果喜歡本作品,請購買並支持正版!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.52,0:01:11.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一學期的期中考試結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.98,0:01:15.98,Warning,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(450,450)\be3\blur3}翻譯 觸手 菜醬 阿虛 校譯 時間 阿虛 後期：風一樣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.37,0:01:14.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 名次上升了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.69,0:01:15.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.75,0:01:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全靠貞子複習會
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.31,0:01:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.46,0:01:22.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.02,0:01:28.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就是學園祭了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.30,0:01:30.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 這是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.10,0:01:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便秘？利尿？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.26,0:01:33.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.06,0:01:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據說這是二年級的黑沼貞子種的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.52,0:01:38.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.68,0:01:40.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊我知道 還見過呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.98,0:01:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說一年級的時候就有各種詛咒的傳說
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.79,0:01:46.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 都有什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.76,0:01:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:51.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年學園祭的主題是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.64,0:01:54.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.96,0:01:59.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是 大家對於班級的節目有什麼提案嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.79,0:02:05.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我也能一起參加就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.27,0:02:11.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣都好啦 趕快決定
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.15,0:02:12.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 我說 我說
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.81,0:02:15.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子的黑魔法咖啡廳 怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.88,0:02:17.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑魔法？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.13,0:02:20.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子在一年級學生當中也相當有名
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.83,0:02:23.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用那些奇怪的藥草泡茶怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.84,0:02:28.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子的心理咨詢室怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.84,0:02:30.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄成占卜那種感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.09,0:02:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子真是長進了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.40,0:02:36.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.27,0:02:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,百鬼夜行怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.10,0:02:39.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.46,0:02:42.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼開始投票
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.60,0:02:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs24\c&HE1EAE7&\3c&H435F50&\pos(608,194)}班\N級\N節\N目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.60,0:02:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs24\c&HE1EAE7&\3c&H435F50&\pos(484,159)}貞\N子\N的\N黑\N魔\N法\N咖\N啡\N廳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.60,0:02:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs24\c&HE1EAE7&\3c&H435F50&\pos(306,310)}鬼\N屋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.60,0:02:46.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs24\c&HE1EAE7&\3c&H435F50&\pos(169,152)}化\N妝\N隊\N列
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.59,0:02:49.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.60,0:02:51.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是蕺菜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.32,0:02:53.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好像有蕺菜茶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.53,0:02:55.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那這個呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.78,0:02:56.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是紫蘇
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.21,0:02:58.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連紫蘇都種啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.55,0:03:01.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想這些或許會比較有用
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:05.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是風早等人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.10,0:03:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.65,0:03:12.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 爽子種了這麼多藥草
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.52,0:03:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.74,0:03:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說 紫蘇在咖啡廳裡能用到嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.96,0:03:46.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:48.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.44,0:03:50.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用來泡茶？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.75,0:03:54.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 倒上熱水的話 什麼都是茶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.36,0:03:56.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子 這個呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.41,0:03:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那個是迷迭香
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.40,0:04:00.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷迭香？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.70,0:04:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然想和他說話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.58,0:04:07.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是該和他說什麼呢 我想不到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.32,0:04:10.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的錯覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.41,0:04:13.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他的距離似乎更遙遠了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.57,0:04:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩個人的距離...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.96,0:04:22.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我 把兩個人的距離拉開了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.45,0:04:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子她 倒是想和風早說話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.34,0:04:33.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早也是 從最近一直都是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.87,0:04:35.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺總是差了那麼點主動
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.28,0:04:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是發生什麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.35,0:04:43.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距離爽子最遠的人 說不定就是風早了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.70,0:04:45.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.68,0:04:48.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得想辦法補救啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.39,0:04:49.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 讓龍...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.58,0:04:50.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要和龍...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.43,0:04:54.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和龍一起去吧 這個週末
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.63,0:04:56.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結婚典禮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.73,0:04:57.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 說這個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.12,0:05:01.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 坐大叔的車一起過去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.95,0:05:03.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾點出發？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.44,0:05:06.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.27,0:05:23.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用眼線筆把睫毛之間的縫隙填滿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.27,0:05:27.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼黑上面的部分要畫粗一些
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.63,0:05:33.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後 眼角處要畫長 略下垂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.11,0:05:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.06,0:05:43.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是 你在搞什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.99,0:05:45.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢 矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.97,0:05:49.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命 救命
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.76,0:05:51.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家已經有一個長成這樣的人偶了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.27,0:05:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論化什麼樣的妝
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.93,0:05:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,底妝才是決定一切的因素
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.14,0:06:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.67,0:06:05.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感謝你了 這麼早跑來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.45,0:06:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用啦 反正也看到那麼有趣的東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.96,0:06:11.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說小千啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.69,0:06:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該做的不是讓眼睛看起來更大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.97,0:06:18.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以讓我試下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.97,0:06:19.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.63,0:06:20.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好誒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.07,0:06:24.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,細長的眼角 才是小千眼睛的魅力之處
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.95,0:06:25.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.23,0:06:27.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把這個當做重點
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.01,0:06:30.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來體現小千的可愛之處
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.58,0:06:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一次對於你來說 也是一個重要的舞台了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.41,0:06:40.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再就是用淡粉色畫高光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.96,0:06:43.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,增加一點柔和感
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.52,0:06:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.77,0:06:47.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直是判若兩人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.33,0:06:55.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.98,0:07:00.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.19,0:07:06.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快上車吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.75,0:07:09.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出發了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.10,0:07:35.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.15,0:07:38.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一輩子都不會丟下小千的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.23,0:07:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.48,0:07:42.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的真的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.34,0:07:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹 遙姐姐 恭喜你們
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.72,0:08:31.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.09,0:08:40.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結婚典禮辦的不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.70,0:08:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.74,0:08:48.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏季的比賽就快到了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.72,0:08:50.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學園祭結束之後就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.41,0:08:53.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好加油 這次一定要贏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.13,0:08:55.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.00,0:08:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.83,0:09:03.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有事找我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.85,0:09:23.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.88,0:09:24.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.10,0:09:25.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為啥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.43,0:09:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.03,0:09:31.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是替我跟風早說幾句好話嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.56,0:09:32.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.24,0:09:35.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就說他百分之百的理解爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.16,0:09:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 你那些好話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.22,0:09:40.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有口無心的東西 我說不出口
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.64,0:09:41.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不想說
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.71,0:09:43.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你這塊死木頭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.97,0:09:44.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辦不到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.37,0:09:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 聽他說說心事倒是可以
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.12,0:09:59.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先聲明 這並不是為了千鶴而做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.63,0:10:02.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我有些在意翔太
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.30,0:10:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算他告訴我了 我也不見得會告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.72,0:10:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 謝謝你的飲料了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.81,0:10:13.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等等 龍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.83,0:10:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太 你不去食堂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.86,0:10:29.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.10,0:10:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把工具送過去之後就去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了 風早
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.35,0:10:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.85,0:10:42.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最期待黑魔法咖啡廳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.23,0:10:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有貞子咨詢室呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.98,0:10:48.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.46,0:10:50.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒有靈感
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.03,0:10:54.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好擔心能不能幫到大家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.70,0:10:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事啦 你只要把想到的事情說出來就好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.66,0:11:03.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯 爽子一看就很擅長這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.32,0:11:08.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會全心全意的去努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.30,0:11:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用紫蘇和老鸛草做混合茶好不好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.42,0:11:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.48,0:11:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,師父
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.53,0:11:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和你說說話 現在有時間嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.20,0:11:45.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥不走尋常路
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.72,0:11:48.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥不走尋常路
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.81,0:11:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚你也別想睡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.83,0:12:00.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔太
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.41,0:12:03.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.00,0:12:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.75,0:12:15.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千鶴說的事情...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.66,0:12:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微問幾句吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.63,0:12:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥 你到底是要和黑沼坦白 還是不坦白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.12,0:12:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 湯灑了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.06,0:12:32.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹啥啊 突然問這個
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.14,0:12:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 只是有點在意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.93,0:12:43.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有點搞不懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.92,0:12:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道該怎樣和她相處
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.02,0:12:50.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以來 黑沼相處的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.16,0:12:54.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從來都只會考慮自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.48,0:12:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是想著要為她做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.91,0:13:01.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然間意識到 我做的事情可能只是在給她添麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.94,0:13:03.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些不知所措了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.99,0:13:08.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前迷茫的時候 都是直接去問她 但現在...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.42,0:13:11.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去問她嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.65,0:13:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想那只會給她添麻煩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.66,0:13:16.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.05,0:13:18.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.03,0:13:19.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 這不是翔太嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.21,0:13:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小子還窩在這裡悠閒的吃飯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.32,0:13:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在食堂吃飯有什麼問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.67,0:13:32.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣跟哥說話 你可是會後悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.26,0:13:36.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老婆正跟人外遇呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.17,0:13:38.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和三浦健人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.10,0:13:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是我老婆
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.37,0:13:50.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也算不上什麼外遇
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.11,0:13:54.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 也就是說...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:13:57.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被人甩了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.40,0:14:01.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被甩了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.65,0:14:02.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.08,0:14:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.08,0:14:12.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還沒去告白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.22,0:14:16.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要把你心中的愛付諸於言語
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.18,0:14:19.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在明媚的陽光下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.86,0:14:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清爽的傾訴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.80,0:14:24.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿出你那如螻蟻一般渺小的勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.73,0:14:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在公園的健身器材邊上傾訴你的愛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.89,0:14:32.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會被這種人看穿
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.57,0:14:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃飽了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.74,0:14:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃飯吃飯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.46,0:14:38.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 龍這麼快就吃完了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.73,0:14:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}比起咖喱 炒飯好吃多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.14,0:14:44.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或許 黑沼還完全沒有察覺到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.33,0:14:49.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 也可能已經知道 卻覺得很為難吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.18,0:14:54.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來 我真的是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.94,0:14:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點都不理解黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.34,0:15:01.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 那又怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.17,0:15:04.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是理所當然嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.78,0:15:08.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為你是誰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.32,0:15:12.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.63,0:15:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說她在哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.13,0:15:18.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.10,0:15:19.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.10,0:15:23.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼的話 就在那個種滿了奇怪的草的花壇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.61,0:15:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.27,0:15:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可喜可賀啊 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.42,0:15:35.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經完全融入新的班級了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.70,0:15:38.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融入班級？我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.08,0:15:44.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.17,0:15:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我夢寐以求的融入班級
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.89,0:15:53.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 自己都沒發現嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.36,0:15:57.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後就不要覺得自己是在班裡被孤立的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.67,0:16:00.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算沒有風早在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.67,0:16:03.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子自己也做的很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.82,0:16:08.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不高興嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.02,0:16:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道你是希望一直被大家孤立
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.36,0:16:14.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直讓風早照顧你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.78,0:16:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.39,0:16:24.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融入班級...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.75,0:16:28.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}帶我玩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.12,0:16:31.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是我的目標
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.35,0:16:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}早晨好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.46,0:16:36.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是我的憧憬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.91,0:16:37.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.82,0:16:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.29,0:16:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他對待我的態度太過自然
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.39,0:16:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我把最基本的事情忘記了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.76,0:16:51.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因為性格陰暗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.03,0:16:54.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以什麼都不做 卻能受到風早的照顧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.96,0:17:00.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受人照顧算是性格陰暗的福利
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.73,0:17:03.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 的確是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.76,0:17:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明應該很高興的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.64,0:17:07.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻又有點驚訝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.57,0:17:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早的那種性格本應該是我的憧憬
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.80,0:17:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種誤會也是不可避免的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.54,0:17:23.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被風早帶著那種笑容搭訕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.80,0:17:27.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 貌似被看穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.64,0:17:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是超能力者師父
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.43,0:17:31.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.45,0:17:33.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得他也沒有惡意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.62,0:17:36.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然沒有惡意 但是他神經也太大條了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.68,0:17:40.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.66,0:17:46.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早會用平等 開朗又清爽的態度對待每一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.41,0:17:50.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是見到我 也會笑著和我打招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.89,0:17:55.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說出自己的心裡話的時候 他也會相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.42,0:17:59.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 對於風早 我才會...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.61,0:18:04.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有生以來第一次沒有感受到與他人之間的隔閡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.07,0:18:07.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.33,0:18:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為他是這樣的一個人 我才會喜歡上他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.12,0:18:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我卻...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.28,0:18:15.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從很久以前就開始
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.34,0:18:18.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無法滿足於此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.89,0:18:22.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我自己都沒有辦法相信...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.63,0:18:27.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這明明只是我自己的錯覺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.97,0:18:30.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.97,0:18:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是錯覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.92,0:18:35.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別 別再說了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.69,0:18:38.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是從自己的嘴裡說出來 也是很讓人傷心的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.93,0:18:40.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.35,0:18:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早 你真是個罪人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.55,0:18:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.71,0:18:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是不要再接近風早會比較好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.58,0:18:55.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是為了你們兩個好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.07,0:18:57.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了我們兩個？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.46,0:18:58.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然是你們兩個了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.90,0:19:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子可以從此獨立 一個人享受自己的青春
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.25,0:19:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早也算是完成自己的任務 可以輕鬆...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.14,0:19:09.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.80,0:19:13.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早他 已經有喜歡的女孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.79,0:19:19.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是早就被甩了的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.31,0:19:26.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本來不想說的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.11,0:19:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你也沒有必要對風早這麼執著吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.28,0:19:33.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不想給他添麻煩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.43,0:19:35.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢 怎麼說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.28,0:19:38.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就當人生重新開始
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.81,0:19:41.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和其他人談談戀愛什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.69,0:19:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後也會有很多開心的事...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.37,0:19:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.05,0:19:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.64,0:19:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來他已經...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.75,0:19:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的已經 有了喜歡的女孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.64,0:19:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.07,0:20:03.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對他這麼認真嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.16,0:20:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.57,0:20:09.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 肯定會有更適合貞子的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.78,0:20:14.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會有事的 真的 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.22,0:20:16.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑的時候很可愛的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.05,0:20:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼淚停不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.00,0:20:21.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只有我一個人的話 什麼都做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.93,0:20:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以來 我真是太過依賴他了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.51,0:20:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.76,0:20:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該更加自信一點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.41,0:20:36.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生也是要多少有多少
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.80,0:20:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不然 選我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.45,0:20:55.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是貞子的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.86,0:20:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我願意
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:26.70,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}どうか今だけは振り向かないで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:26.70,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}這一刻 請你不要回頭看我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.24,0:21:39.67,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}夕暮れさわぐ風　触れそうな距離
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.24,0:21:39.67,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}在傍晚搖曳的風中 近在咫尺的距離
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.19,0:21:52.70,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君を見つめてる　ずっと
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.19,0:21:52.70,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我一直 凝視著你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.18,0:21:58.96,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.18,0:21:58.96,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}喜歡你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.90,0:22:05.61,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君が好きで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.90,0:22:05.61,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}一直喜歡著你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.58,0:22:11.43,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}叶わない恋でもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.58,0:22:11.43,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使這份戀情永遠也不能實現
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.57,0:22:14.75,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}傷ついてもいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.57,0:22:14.75,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}即使會讓我受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.91,0:22:19.64,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}何度でも伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.91,0:22:19.64,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}我也想一次又一次的讓你感受到這份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.90,0:22:23.51,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}君に届け
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.90,0:22:23.51,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3\blur3\fad(100,100)}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.86,0:22:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs24\3c&H000007&\c&HF3F3F3&\pos(578,339)\fn汉仪丫丫体简}第6話 好意與麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.26,0:22:31.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本以為這才是理所當然
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.25,0:22:34.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一話 好意與麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:24:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H904F0D&\3c&HE1CFCA&\be3\fs20\pos(823,371)\fad(450,450)}異\N域\N字\N幕\N組\N長\N期\N招\N募\N翻\N譯\N校\N譯\N人\N員
