[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00f6eafe,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: endshengyoubiaoti,华康布丁体W12(P),32,&H00a074f4,&H000000ff,&H00e7cff9,&H004609cc,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFMaruGothic-Md,32,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,10,10,10,128
Style: edj,DFGMaruMoji-SL,33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00f7f7fa,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00c77638,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,微软雅黑,38,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,20,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,华康少女文字W5(P),33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(550,500)}异域字幕组作品\N{\be1\fad(0,500)}WWW.YYDM.COM
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}沐浴著溫暖的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}優しい日だまりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}鈴聲長長地響起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}チャイムがディレイする
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迎面輕撫而來的微風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}頬を撫でる風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}讓人情不自禁深深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}息吹は深くなっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迂迴的眼淚 注定的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}遠回りの涙　名前付けた明日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}宛如交織重疊的線條
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}重ねるみたい　いろんのライン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}年少天真無邪時的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}あどけない頃な気持ちも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}曾經燦爛歡笑的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}弾け飛ぶほど笑い会えた日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}我都小心翼翼留存在心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}大切に育ていているように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}穿越斷點的光陰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}途切れ途切れの時を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}帶給我許多從未體驗過的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}たくさんの初めてをくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}將你和我緊緊相連
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}繋がってゆけ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}届け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,327)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(350,400,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,238)}{\fs70}{\c&H74AFEB&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1150,1200,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,282)}{\fs70}{\c&HC080FF&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(750,800,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,194)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1550,1600,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,372)}{\fs70}{\c&H7CCFD3&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(50,100,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(530,360)}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}異\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}域\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}字\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}幕\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.93,0:01:04.93,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HB68A7D&\3c&HF7F6F4&\bord1\4c&HC6A599&}第22話 聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.43,0:01:19.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.61,0:01:21.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.66,0:01:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12月已經過了一半了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.96,0:01:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.09,0:01:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.55,0:01:44.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期末考試結束後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.04,0:01:50.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生了很多事情的第二學期就只剩下結業典禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:57.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千好像輕鬆了不少 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.55,0:01:59.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好的和龍的哥哥見了一面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.63,0:02:04.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧了龍把他叫來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.79,0:02:11.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千之後很害羞的告訴我們 她被龍安慰了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.11,0:02:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了 考試也結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.13,0:02:17.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.50,0:02:21.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點也不好 要補習啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次也是沒轍嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.31,0:02:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得爽子專門給我做了筆記
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.04,0:02:26.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs26}(小千的筆記 加油噢~~)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.39,0:02:30.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒幫上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.70,0:02:32.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果只有我沒及格
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.51,0:02:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.00,0:04:14.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,本片字幕由異域字幕組製作，僅供試看之用，請於試看後24小時內刪除。若因私自散佈造成法律問題，本組概不負責。如果喜歡本作品，請購買並支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.83,0:02:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.12,0:02:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,補習在聖誕節前能完嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.94,0:02:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.70,0:02:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 就是那個戀人們互訴衷腸的輕飄飄的日子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.87,0:02:52.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個喜歡節日的孩子居然在自暴自棄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.82,0:02:56.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛好學校在聖誕節前夜放假
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.67,0:02:59.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,單身的人都來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.47,0:03:00.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慶祝聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.32,0:03:04.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍啊城啊他們也說要在聚聚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.30,0:03:05.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.10,0:03:06.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.27,0:03:09.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交換禮物 吃些美食
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.11,0:03:10.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有美食
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.72,0:03:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也慰勞一下補習的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.60,0:03:17.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了 風早 多叫些女生哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.00,0:03:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還要玩國王遊戲 Yeah
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.10,0:03:22.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駁回
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.26,0:03:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.04,0:03:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.12,0:21:04.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,人員表 翻譯 瑤瑤 老虎 校譯 時間 阿虛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.73,0:03:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,參加 參加資格呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.50,0:03:48.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了 大家一起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.23,0:03:50.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子在做什麼禱告麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.09,0:03:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年矢野也很閒呢 聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.51,0:03:57.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很閒沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.63,0:04:03.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所謂大家啊 就是我們都去 黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.80,0:04:05.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.28,0:04:10.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和小千爽子一起過聖誕今年可能是第一次也是最後一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.37,0:04:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年我就去不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.54,0:04:16.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不好說哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.77,0:04:22.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也被歸在「大家」中了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.72,0:04:25.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像往常一樣 貼一張紙出去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.61,0:04:28.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,參加的人把名字寫在這上面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.89,0:04:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.27,0:04:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.74,0:04:36.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.50,0:04:39.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以和大家一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.54,0:04:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs26}(聖誕節晚會參加者 自備禮物 800日元左右 參加者名字若干)
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.59,0:04:58.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以把名字寫到這上面去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.65,0:05:02.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直很憧憬的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.99,0:05:09.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦 家裡也要過聖誕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.00,0:05:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家問問爸媽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.55,0:05:20.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒回家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.45,0:05:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.25,0:05:39.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去嗎 黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.69,0:05:44.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去問問父母再決定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.57,0:05:44.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.37,0:05:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.26,0:05:59.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我是很想去的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.98,0:06:04.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和家人以外的人過聖誕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.19,0:06:07.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和朋友一起過聖誕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.48,0:06:10.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.72,0:06:25.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和風早同學過的第一個聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.99,0:06:33.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.67,0:06:35.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要給小千圍裙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.18,0:06:38.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送綾音杯墊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.32,0:06:42.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕節禮物我早做好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.78,0:06:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送爸爸腹帶 媽媽拖鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.60,0:06:49.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交換禮物準備什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.63,0:06:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 先要問問我能不能去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.06,0:06:54.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給風早同學...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.47,0:07:05.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 那種禮物再怎麼說也太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.11,0:07:07.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能送手編圍巾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.38,0:07:12.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且就算織了也沒辦法給他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.30,0:07:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定沒辦法給他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.35,0:07:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是織一下應該沒什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.66,0:07:29.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是織一下 織一下而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.21,0:07:33.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 你爸回來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.41,0:07:34.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.06,0:07:38.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去問問能不能參加聖誕節晚會
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.86,0:07:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 歡迎回家 那個聖誕...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.05,0:07:51.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 今年還沒有問聖誕老人要禮物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.82,0:07:54.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快點的話聖誕老人可就不管了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.33,0:08:00.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就 筆記本和自動鉛筆芯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.45,0:08:04.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種爸爸也能買
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.15,0:08:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕老人說今年要奢侈一次
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.10,0:08:16.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就鉛筆盒還有上等自動鉛一隻 拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.70,0:08:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟爸爸說管什麼用啊 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.58,0:08:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好寫在紙上掛起來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.98,0:08:28.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.07,0:08:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年爽子做的雞肉很好吃呢 媽媽做的也很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.81,0:08:39.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 很期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.68,0:08:42.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年的聖誕節前夜是週末呢 爸爸也要早上就開始幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.84,0:08:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.35,0:08:47.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.83,0:08:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋糕就交給爽子了 我會很期待的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.31,0:08:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子是好孩子 聖誕老人每年都會來的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.52,0:09:01.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不出口
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.70,0:09:06.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.69,0:09:15.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 那個 爸爸媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.63,0:09:21.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子的預產期 其實是24日呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.08,0:09:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直沒有出生我本來很擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.82,0:09:28.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是健健康康的長這麼大了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.20,0:09:31.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀 真是懷念呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.28,0:09:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果在三十那天出生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.50,0:09:38.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我們來說爽子就是聖誕節禮物呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.22,0:09:42.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦 爸爸你哭什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.80,0:09:45.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.57,0:09:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 你剛才想說什麼來著 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.37,0:09:59.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.93,0:10:13.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是說不出口
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.89,0:10:21.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 你不去 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.83,0:10:25.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸好像很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.20,0:10:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.62,0:10:29.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微露一下面嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.16,0:10:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們家是從早上開始過一整天的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.49,0:10:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.62,0:10:40.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個 雖然早了一點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.54,0:10:46.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是圍裙啊 去龍家幫忙的時候穿它好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.44,0:10:49.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給綾音的是杯墊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.59,0:10:54.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可愛啊 這難道是你自己做的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.83,0:10:55.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.75,0:10:58.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不大好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.41,0:11:00.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真強啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.59,0:11:03.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.43,0:11:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了 我會用的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.19,0:11:06.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們都很喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.98,0:11:10.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.92,0:11:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是爽子送的 不錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.64,0:11:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕節禮物哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.43,0:11:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 好羨慕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.72,0:11:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他會收下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.27,0:11:36.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒可能啦 真是大不敬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.72,0:11:40.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過這樣好嗎 不在聖誕節當天送嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.59,0:11:44.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子說她不去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.24,0:11:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子爸爸貌似很期待聖誕節
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.43,0:11:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.53,0:11:55.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.00,0:11:59.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.58,0:12:04.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.64,0:12:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.73,0:12:09.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.05,0:12:10.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.08,0:12:14.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕聚會的店預約定好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.59,0:12:16.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你來下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.14,0:12:18.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.44,0:12:22.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.21,0:12:25.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年錯開日子開吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.88,0:12:29.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯沒錯 25號也沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.97,0:12:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩的開心點
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.58,0:12:39.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得他們邀請我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.90,0:12:51.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年再參加吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.62,0:13:06.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後到了12月24號 聖誕前夜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.80,0:13:09.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,織好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.90,0:13:13.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不能給他 但總覺得很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.12,0:13:18.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把給父母的禮物藏起來 嚇他們一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.08,0:13:22.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 爸爸 起來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.81,0:13:23.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.30,0:13:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷死了冷死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.92,0:13:35.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗手間空著了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.77,0:13:38.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很適合你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.16,0:13:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 剛好合適
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.49,0:13:43.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 謝謝你的聖誕禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.23,0:13:51.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還記得我以前說頭很冷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸你的額頭很寬呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.81,0:13:56.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是暖和啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.38,0:13:58.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想要這樣的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.31,0:13:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你了 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.12,0:14:01.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.32,0:14:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.87,0:14:11.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.05,0:14:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實本來想再等一會兒給你們的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.08,0:14:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給 媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.50,0:14:18.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是沒有辦法給他了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.44,0:14:22.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然是有人用比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.89,0:14:26.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他們是那麼的高興
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.29,0:14:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在大家都玩的開心嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.45,0:14:40.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.91,0:14:43.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開心麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.66,0:14:46.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.08,0:14:51.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電話響了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.49,0:14:52.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去接
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.16,0:14:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.96,0:14:59.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽不到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.81,0:15:01.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.44,0:15:02.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.06,0:15:04.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.74,0:15:06.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.06,0:15:09.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想爽子聖誕節在幹什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.46,0:15:11.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然沒有爽子覺得很寂寞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.09,0:15:13.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在換矢野聽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.79,0:15:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給 矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.93,0:15:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.28,0:15:19.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綾音
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.05,0:15:23.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點擔心你會不會覺得寂寞 沒問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.13,0:15:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微來下也好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.25,0:15:31.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相對的 現在給你聖誕禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.37,0:15:36.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.36,0:15:38.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.96,0:15:41.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑沼麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.47,0:15:46.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑沼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.44,0:15:56.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.00,0:15:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.54,0:16:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發不出聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.16,0:16:21.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 媽媽來打聲招呼 換我聽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.14,0:16:25.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我是爽子的母親
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.72,0:16:27.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你一直照顧爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.31,0:16:29.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 啊 晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.47,0:16:33.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那邊很開心嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.33,0:16:35.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽 媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.50,0:16:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 稍微來這裡下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.57,0:16:42.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.22,0:16:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.07,0:16:46.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果爽黑沼來的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.86,0:16:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家就更加開心了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.07,0:16:52.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.01,0:16:57.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一會兒 可以去下大家那裡一會兒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.01,0:16:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果黑沼來的話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.79,0:17:03.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會更加 更加的開心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.93,0:17:09.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打開吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.02,0:17:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是聖誕老人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.85,0:17:14.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是爸爸給你的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.72,0:17:15.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打開吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.90,0:17:26.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情要早點說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.96,0:17:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果回來晚的話 我會打電話給你的 帶上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.19,0:17:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電已經充好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.89,0:17:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.11,0:17:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子走了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.90,0:17:47.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一天終於來了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.57,0:17:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是第一回合開始前的熱身哦 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.00,0:17:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來得及嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.41,0:18:01.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就到此為止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.20,0:18:04.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待明年人數減少
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.55,0:18:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乾杯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.93,0:18:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來不及了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.48,0:18:20.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.26,0:18:24.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使這樣我也想去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.26,0:18:27.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去2次卡拉ok的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.00,0:18:30.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 風早
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.41,0:18:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.56,0:19:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你或許會來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.42,0:19:16.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.48,0:19:38.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然聖誕聚會和互換禮物都結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.54,0:19:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是給黑沼的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.79,0:19:50.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能意義並不大
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.92,0:20:04.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.31,0:20:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然還不知道怎麼用
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.87,0:20:20.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.35,0:20:34.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發送
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.67,0:20:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一個手機裡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.49,0:20:42.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一個登錄的是風早同學的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.72,0:20:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.84,0:20:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是沒趕上聖誕聚會
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.86,0:20:52.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 我也有禮物和你交換...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.01,0:20:54.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧 真的麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.97,0:20:59.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 圍脖麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.60,0:21:03.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小小的奇跡
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.09,0:21:05.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,些許的陰差陽錯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.57,0:21:10.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.70,0:21:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聖誕快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いかない　それが答えてなんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 那就是回答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シャボン玉　飛ばそう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡泡 飄飄浮浮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空まではきっと届かない　うちに壊れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還未到達天空就破滅消散而去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま誰知りたいの永遠じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們想要的永遠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままずっと　いていたいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管想要永遠留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只找尋到了屬於我的唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.94,0:22:34.67,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(655,360)}第23話 兩個人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.06,0:22:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,響起的鐘聲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.50,0:22:30.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一份小小的留戀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一話 兩個人
