[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00f6eafe,&H000000ff,&H00e1c4ee,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: endshengyoubiaoti,华康布丁体W12(P),32,&H00a074f4,&H000000ff,&H00e7cff9,&H004609cc,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFMaruGothic-Md,32,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,10,10,10,128
Style: edj,DFGMaruMoji-SL,33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00f7f7fa,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,8,10,10,10,128
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00c77638,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,微软雅黑,38,&H00a08708,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,20,&H00ffffff,&Hff0000ff,&H00000000,&Hff000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,华康少女文字W5(P),33,&H005490d7,&H000000ff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(550,500)}异域字幕组作品\N{\be1\fad(0,500)}WWW.YYDM.COM
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}沐浴著溫暖的陽光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}優しい日だまりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}鈴聲長長地響起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}チャイムがディレイする
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迎面輕撫而來的微風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}頬を撫でる風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}讓人情不自禁深深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}息吹は深くなっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迂迴的眼淚 注定的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}遠回りの涙　名前付けた明日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}宛如交織重疊的線條
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}重ねるみたい　いろんのライン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}年少天真無邪時的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}あどけない頃な気持ちも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}曾經燦爛歡笑的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}弾け飛ぶほど笑い会えた日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}我都小心翼翼留存在心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}大切に育ていているように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}穿越斷點的光陰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}途切れ途切れの時を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}帶給我許多從未體驗過的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}たくさんの初めてをくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}將你和我緊緊相連
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}繋がってゆけ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}好想告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}届け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,327)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(350,400,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,238)}{\fs70}{\c&H74AFEB&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1150,1200,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,282)}{\fs70}{\c&HC080FF&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(750,800,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,194)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1550,1600,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,372)}{\fs70}{\c&H7CCFD3&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(50,100,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(530,360)}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}異\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}域\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}字\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}幕\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}組
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:02:40.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,本片字幕由異域字幕組製作，僅供試看之用，請於試看後24小時內刪除。若因私自散佈造成法律問題，本組概不負責。如果喜歡本作品，請購買並支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.87,0:01:04.79,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HD8F0E8&\4c&H616484&\pos(420,389)}第五話 決心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.52,0:01:07.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.55,0:01:09.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.46,0:01:11.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.41,0:01:15.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 飯都掉在桌子上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.77,0:01:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.45,0:01:22.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在想考試的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:25.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 明天就要考試了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.18,0:01:28.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我吃飽了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.01,0:01:30.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.93,0:01:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.55,0:01:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.78,0:01:35.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到矢野同學 吉田同學
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.08,0:01:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有風早同學的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.80,0:01:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該怎麼辦才好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.35,0:01:48.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.12,0:19:25.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,翻譯:瑤瑤 老虎　校譯:キョン　時間:キョン　後期:風一樣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.61,0:01:50.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為是考試期間
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.33,0:01:52.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,座位是按照學號排的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.16,0:01:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在我平時的座位上是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.89,0:01:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野同學
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.71,0:02:01.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫不介意的坐在我的座位上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.56,0:02:04.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明因為我的錯 給她招來奇怪的謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.64,0:02:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是這樣 矢野 吉田還有風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.36,0:02:15.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從來沒有討厭或者害怕過我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.15,0:02:20.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他們都一直很溫柔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.38,0:02:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.46,0:02:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.13,0:02:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 對哦 矢野你坐的是貞子的位子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.01,0:02:32.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.50,0:02:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.97,0:02:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常就算被人躲著也會先向每個人打招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.92,0:02:41.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是對任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.34,0:02:44.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這次她卻連理都不理我們就坐到座位上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.47,0:02:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.95,0:02:47.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我也不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:52.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說 這不是往常的貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.99,0:02:53.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.18,0:02:56.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離開了一直坐的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.28,0:03:00.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個座位彷彿從來就沒有存在過似的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.13,0:03:04.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初就沒有存在過似的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.15,0:03:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像就像夢一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.61,0:03:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺很遙遠
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.30,0:03:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.74,0:03:14.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實不想給大家添麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.41,0:03:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是希望能幫到大家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.23,0:03:22.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我和矢野還有吉田同學的誤會還沒有解開
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.69,0:03:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算之後能找到散佈謠言的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.47,0:03:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解開了誤會
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.80,0:03:31.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我還在他們的身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.97,0:03:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是會像這次一樣傷害到她們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.32,0:03:37.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傷害到如此溫柔的她們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.41,0:03:40.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說誤會可以解開
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.08,0:03:47.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不知道該如何安慰已經受到傷害的她們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.17,0:03:49.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.63,0:03:52.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想還是回到從前吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.07,0:03:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從大家身邊離開吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.27,0:03:57.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一定是最好的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.65,0:04:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田同學用過那本筆記了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.45,0:04:05.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能稍微能幫到她就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.44,0:04:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野同學
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.71,0:04:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經能講很多鬼故事了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.75,0:04:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然想讓矢野同學第一個聽聽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.59,0:04:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不可能了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.45,0:04:23.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.16,0:04:26.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.30,0:04:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 一直都很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.51,0:04:38.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直尋求的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.77,0:04:40.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直憧憬的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.76,0:04:42.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是我...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.62,0:04:47.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經不知道一個人該如何走下去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.66,0:04:51.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不小心知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.16,0:04:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了被人溫柔對待的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.10,0:04:54.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要對別人溫柔的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.44,0:04:59.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該如何回到從前 我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.73,0:05:01.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼一個人能活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.08,0:05:04.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼能那麼若無其事的活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.83,0:05:07.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.33,0:05:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切 都已經忘記
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.62,0:05:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.02,0:05:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暑假的第一天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.55,0:05:40.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一天也像現在一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.25,0:05:42.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早同學在這裡等著我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.71,0:05:44.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是無法接受
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.11,0:05:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然不討厭我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.73,0:05:48.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那為什麼要躲著我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.00,0:05:56.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要...和我說話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.38,0:06:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是說不出口
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.40,0:06:07.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本說不出違心的話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.12,0:06:08.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.78,0:06:11.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 讓你的人氣下降了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.46,0:06:11.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 等下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.97,0:06:13.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.92,0:06:16.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把話說清楚的話 我是不會明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.32,0:06:22.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在你們的身邊的話 你們的人氣就會下降
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.73,0:06:24.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人氣 誰說的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.65,0:06:26.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謠言這麼傳的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.30,0:06:27.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.13,0:06:30.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是人氣還是謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.78,0:06:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都和我的意願完全無關嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.52,0:06:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是應該由黑沼決定的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.03,0:06:39.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是應該由我決定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.87,0:06:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會做我想做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.83,0:06:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和黑沼聊天就聊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.30,0:06:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想和黑沼聊天的話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.04,0:06:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不會像這樣和你說話了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.52,0:06:58.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謠言怎麼樣都隨它去好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.79,0:07:01.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我而言
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.62,0:07:05.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所看到的黑沼就是黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.08,0:07:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所一直尋求的就是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.89,0:07:16.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像矢野 吉田還有風早同學這樣的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.72,0:07:19.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直憧憬著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.56,0:07:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珍視他人的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.91,0:07:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他人所珍視的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.43,0:07:34.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜下來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.77,0:07:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.74,0:07:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛好覺得喉嚨幹得不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.33,0:07:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就不客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.24,0:07:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.24,0:07:54.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到剛才為止
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.25,0:07:57.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心情還是那麼的絕望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.18,0:07:58.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不可思議
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.01,0:08:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要看到風早同學微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.33,0:08:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道為什麼 心情立刻就放晴了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.44,0:08:08.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心裡就能鬆一口氣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.42,0:08:09.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我而言
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.95,0:08:13.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所看到的黑沼就是黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.41,0:08:15.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.25,0:08:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像在對我說 留在我身邊也沒關係哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.17,0:08:20.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.71,0:08:23.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.17,0:08:26.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為矢野和吉田的謠言才變得那麼拘謹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.70,0:08:30.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果換個立場的話你會怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.68,0:08:34.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或者矢野 吉田
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.54,0:08:37.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為在意和黑沼走的近了就會人氣下降
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.06,0:08:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就疏遠你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.95,0:08:43.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.13,0:08:46.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和大家在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.14,0:08:52.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田她們可能也這麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.81,0:08:56.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果還是要看對方的想法嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.27,0:08:59.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我不清楚吉田她們的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.03,0:09:01.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但突然被避開了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.82,0:09:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可能會變的不安
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.56,0:09:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少 我就很不安
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.01,0:09:09.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱 抱抱抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.97,0:09:10.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.97,0:09:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.75,0:09:15.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次絕對不可以了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.00,0:09:19.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今有過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.86,0:09:21.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不允許我靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.58,0:09:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是不允許我避開的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.00,0:09:26.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.16,0:09:32.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直只是一個人在不斷的想
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.39,0:09:34.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 一定要去問問她們的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.86,0:09:38.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對 不說出來的話是不會明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.53,0:09:41.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想說出來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.23,0:09:43.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對矢野和吉田同學說...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.81,0:09:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望她們能聽下...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.16,0:09:48.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.48,0:09:51.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經想好要對誰說了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.27,0:09:59.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會去和吉田 矢野同學說的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.15,0:10:04.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和她們 不僅是同班同學
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.93,0:10:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能 能成為朋友的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.14,0:10:12.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我會為能成為她們的朋友而努力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.35,0:10:15.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.92,0:10:17.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.88,0:10:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.52,0:10:29.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.70,0:10:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的話語
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.55,0:10:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的微笑 一直推動著我前進
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.38,0:10:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.55,0:10:47.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑沼 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.98,0:10:49.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.60,0:10:52.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風早同學
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.42,0:10:55.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.94,0:10:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.71,0:10:59.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.52,0:11:07.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.67,0:11:08.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.01,0:11:11.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回家準備考試吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.64,0:11:14.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正準備去圖書館學
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.43,0:11:17.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不可貌相 是個認真的傢伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.05,0:11:21.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來都怪你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.57,0:11:22.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:25.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候沒有你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.65,0:11:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼莫名其妙的話啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.12,0:11:30.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒來又會怎樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.82,0:11:36.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒來的話 就能聽到貞子最後說什麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.81,0:11:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.11,0:11:41.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.15,0:11:42.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別怪其他人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.15,0:11:44.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不知道發生了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.07,0:11:48.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪別人也解決不了問題
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.67,0:11:52.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後肯定還會有很多不講理的事發生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.57,0:11:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最終只有靠你自己解決才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.11,0:11:57.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠自己
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.42,0:12:00.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算原因是大爺我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.34,0:12:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己想辦法解決吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.37,0:12:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有話說 卷子給龍了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.71,0:12:11.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種東西 我去燒了它
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.53,0:12:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.20,0:12:16.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別怪其他人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.07,0:12:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.80,0:12:23.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想被小痞說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.99,0:12:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是貞子在讀的書嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.03,0:12:34.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.42,0:12:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個也借過了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.40,0:12:46.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼全是些日本的鬼怪故事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.95,0:12:48.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好傻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.91,0:12:52.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不如就朝那種角色發展如何 怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.17,0:12:58.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只不過是隨便說說而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.66,0:13:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是認真過度啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.96,0:13:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 垂頭喪氣中啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.28,0:13:14.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要我安慰你一下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.58,0:13:16.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.81,0:13:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可沒在垂頭喪氣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.54,0:13:22.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小時候做錯事被趕出來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.45,0:13:24.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是這樣窩在玄關鬱悶嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.31,0:13:26.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真煩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.87,0:13:28.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼 你是跑來的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.76,0:13:31.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 小痞的全日練習任務
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.46,0:13:36.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這垂頭喪氣的原因不會是那個「不良少女」的謠言吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.41,0:13:38.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種謠言 屁都不是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.77,0:13:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.59,0:13:44.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我腦袋不太靈光
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.83,0:13:46.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼想都不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.72,0:13:50.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子是貞子 還是暗黑貞子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.71,0:13:52.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是不知所云呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.07,0:13:54.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就是說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.95,0:13:58.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說謠言是貞子散佈的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.96,0:14:01.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙怎麼散佈謠言啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.22,0:14:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自言自語嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.65,0:14:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那樣 謠言就成了貞子在喃喃自語什麼的了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.84,0:14:11.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那人不是沒什麼可以說話的對象嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.82,0:14:15.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 是這樣的 一定是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.10,0:14:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是單純
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.45,0:14:22.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來她和不認識的人說過話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.64,0:14:26.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的還是「和我們不是朋友」之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.27,0:14:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那樣子也像是喜歡我們
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.79,0:14:31.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後又好像要避開我們
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.03,0:14:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子啊 「對不起」到底什麼意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.94,0:14:40.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候到底問什麼沒回答「喜歡你們」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.46,0:14:43.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為不喜歡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.61,0:14:49.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又是什麼 討厭我們 利用我們
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.81,0:14:53.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰知道 還可以解釋成「無所謂」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.52,0:14:58.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒準還有別的解釋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.89,0:15:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別的 別的是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.36,0:15:02.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.80,0:15:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道就去問本人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.21,0:15:09.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果回答「無所謂」我就來安慰你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.21,0:15:10.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.15,0:15:11.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.09,0:15:24.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}(給吉田同學的要點筆記)
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.01,0:15:26.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 別的解釋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.54,0:15:30.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫得超容易懂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.36,0:15:34.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為是專門給我寫的筆記嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.96,0:15:37.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}(吉田同學 加油)
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.77,0:15:43.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子 畫的好難看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.59,0:15:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰會為了我做這麼麻煩的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.98,0:16:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 現在能出來一下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.16,0:16:09.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考試怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.07,0:16:13.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有貞子教過的部分答出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.71,0:16:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.93,0:16:20.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自從不開心的事發生以來 貞子就沒笑過
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.87,0:16:25.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的貞子 本應該很幸福呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.54,0:16:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起準備考試的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.75,0:16:29.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子她笑的很開心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.80,0:16:33.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 她笑了 嚇我一跳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.39,0:16:40.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.29,0:16:44.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,習慣了總是被人躲著
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.40,0:16:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經覺得那才是正常的了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.18,0:16:51.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事 真是讓人想哭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.22,0:16:52.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是個溫柔的好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.60,0:16:56.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才沒辦法不管
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.90,0:17:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 習慣著周圍人的態度
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.88,0:17:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難以理解別人的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.89,0:17:06.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對自己的感覺也開始變得遲鈍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.95,0:17:10.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種感覺我也能稍微明白點
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.47,0:17:13.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以看到那孩子那麼自然的笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.47,0:17:16.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.18,0:17:20.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那樣想的啊 矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.14,0:17:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別哭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.76,0:17:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.37,0:17:28.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道小千會那麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.28,0:17:31.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.52,0:17:34.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本以為自己很瞭解貞子的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.27,0:17:39.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但實際上卻是對她一無所知 自己還悶悶不樂的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.28,0:17:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們之間不是也有很多不瞭解的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.59,0:17:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野 我們的感覺都沒有和貞子說過呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.76,0:17:56.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是這樣想的 貞子也不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.71,0:18:01.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貞子她說的「對不起」的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.96,0:18:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不是朋友」的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.10,0:18:07.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些話的後續
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.07,0:18:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們問了 貞子她會怎麼回答呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.33,0:18:21.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初還以為她是絕對不會跟我們扯上關係的一類人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.38,0:18:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果我們滿腦子都是貞子的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.49,0:18:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啊 討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.28,0:18:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底要讓我們煩惱到什麼程度你才開心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.17,0:18:32.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一心想著貞子的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.39,0:18:36.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是已經很喜歡她了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.57,0:18:42.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果問她「是不是朋友」的話 有點微妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.34,0:18:46.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣不已經是朋友了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.42,0:18:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們居然能因為貞子的事情這樣煩惱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.75,0:18:58.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自已之外的人的心情 不問是不知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.57,0:19:00.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的心情也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.60,0:19:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好好說出來也無法傳達給對方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.92,0:19:07.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因為不知道才更想瞭解彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.25,0:19:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能這樣想就很高興
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.05,0:19:13.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在 對著這樣迷茫的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.95,0:19:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得很高興能結識那些讓我那麼想的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.76,0:19:26.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見到矢野同學和吉田同學以後
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.83,0:19:29.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就說「能稍微說說話嗎」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.56,0:19:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是休息的時間要準備考試
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.36,0:19:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放學之後
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.35,0:19:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 她們可能要預習明天的課程
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.13,0:19:43.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊好像有什麼聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.53,0:19:45.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 別說了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.38,0:19:48.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很緊張 卻不討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.65,0:19:50.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經想好要對誰說了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.34,0:19:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可以傾訴的對象了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.83,0:19:55.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以講心裡話了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.60,0:19:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對矢野同學和吉田同學
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.61,0:20:00.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了 我今天的考試很糟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.34,0:20:02.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(427,432)}我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.55,0:20:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭了 為了做心理準備一不小心待了這麼久
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.92,0:20:07.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 不是有個貞子的謠言麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.82,0:20:10.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把矢野和吉田當做靠山的那個
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.74,0:20:14.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.13,0:20:15.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.94,0:20:18.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是誤會
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.21,0:20:29.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我並沒有把矢野同學和吉田同學當做靠山
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.69,0:20:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.86,0:20:33.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 那是假的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.78,0:20:37.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢野同學和吉田同學是很溫柔的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.73,0:20:38.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出現了 貞子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.13,0:20:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溫柔啥啊 這孩子在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.30,0:20:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想和我們聊天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.10,0:20:45.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還盯著這邊看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.29,0:20:48.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就長這個樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.50,0:20:50.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 所以矢野同學和吉田同學...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.64,0:20:54.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是煩人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.67,0:20:57.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的 不就是矢野和吉田
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.97,0:20:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.78,0:21:03.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個不良少女和風流少女是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.88,0:21:25.87,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.88,0:21:25.87,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.83,0:21:36.19,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いかない　それが答えてなんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.83,0:21:36.19,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 那就是回答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.44,0:21:39.60,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シャボン玉　飛ばそう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.44,0:21:39.60,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡泡 飄飄浮浮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.13,0:21:47.88,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空まではきっと届かない　うちに壊れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.13,0:21:47.88,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還未到達天空就破滅消散而去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.24,0:21:53.41,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま誰知りたいの永遠じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.24,0:21:53.41,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們想要的永遠
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.67,0:22:01.07,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままずっと　いていたいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.67,0:22:01.07,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管想要永遠留在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.43,0:22:12.34,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.43,0:22:12.34,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飛滿了紙飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.15,0:22:21.88,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.15,0:22:21.88,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只找尋到了屬於我的唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.77,0:22:34.66,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(680,360)}第六話 朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.24,0:22:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要消除的誤解
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.33,0:22:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕不會退讓的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.07,0:22:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一話 朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.20,0:22:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.36,0:22:45.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在今天的放送中 好想告訴你的特邀嘉賓椿姬彩菜作為聲優出場了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.71,0:22:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家發覺了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.72,0:22:49.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個場景
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.37,0:22:57.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊好像有什麼聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.65,0:22:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 別說了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.53,0:23:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很緊張 卻不討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.74,0:23:03.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.69,0:23:07.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次挑戰聲優的椿姬小姐非常努力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.06,0:23:11.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想去試試的說
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.83,0:23:19.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我們下周再見 告訴你
