[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: title,汉仪丫丫体简,60,&H00F6EAFE,&H000000FF,&H00E1C4EE,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: endshengyoubiaoti,华康布丁体W12(P),32,&H00A074F4,&H000000FF,&H00E7CFF9,&H004609CC,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: opj,DFMaruGothic-Md,32,&H00A08708,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: edj,DFGMaruMoji-SL,33,&H005490D7,&H000000FF,&H00F7F7FA,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,4,1,8,10,10,10,1
Style: Default,方正粗圆简体,32,&H00C77638,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: logo,方正粗倩简体,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,50,1
Style: opc,Microsoft YaHei,38,&H00A08708,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Warning,汉仪琥珀体简,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: edc,华康少女文字W5(P),33,&H005490D7,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,4,1,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(550,500)}异域字幕组作品\N{\be1\fad(0,500)}WWW.YYDM.COM
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}沐浴着温暖的阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.49,0:00:05.98,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}優しい日だまりに
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}铃声长长地响起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:10.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}チャイムがディレイする
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迎面轻抚而来的微风
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.50,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}頬を撫でる風
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}让人情不自禁深深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.70,0:00:18.32,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}息吹は深くなっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}迂回的眼泪 注定的明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:23.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}遠回りの涙　名前付けた明日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}宛如交织重叠的线条
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.38,0:00:27.00,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}重ねるみたい　いろんのライン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}年少天真无邪时的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.58,0:00:32.22,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}あどけない頃な気持ちも
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}曾经灿烂欢笑的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.56,0:00:36.42,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}弾け飛ぶほど笑い会えた日も
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}我都小心翼翼留存在心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.73,0:00:43.57,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}大切に育ていているように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}穿越断点的光阴
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:47.47,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}途切れ途切れの時を越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}带给我许多从未体验过的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:51.80,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}たくさんの初めてをくれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}将你和我紧紧相连
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:54.52,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}繋がってゆけ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}好想告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.85,0:00:57.16,opj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be10}届け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,327)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(350,400,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,238)}{\fs70}{\c&H74AFEB&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1150,1200,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,282)}{\fs70}{\c&HC080FF&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(750,800,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,194)}{\fs70}{\c&HBBBF60&}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(1550,1600,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}{\blur8}{\pos(530,372)}{\fs70}{\c&H7CCFD3&}{\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(4000,4250,\alpha&HFF&)}{\t(50,100,\blur0)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.33,0:00:11.00,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(530,360)}{\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1550,1600,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}异\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(1150,1200,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}域\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(750,800,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}字\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(350,400,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}幕\N{\r\blur8\alpha&HFF&\t(0,50,\alpha&H00&\blur0)}{\t(5300,5600,\alpha&HFF&)}组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.02,0:01:04.76,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\3c&HAA8E86&}第23话 两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.90,0:01:38.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.59,0:01:55.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.47,0:01:59.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是现实
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.31,0:02:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.49,0:02:14.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.78,0:02:17.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.06,0:02:19.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明受打击了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.14,0:02:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明吓了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.62,0:02:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸的礼物也能让你开心吗 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.10,0:02:30.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子的话去拿晨报了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.91,0:02:32.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子 爽...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.00,0:04:14.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,本片字幕由异域字幕组制作，仅供试看之用，请于试看后24小时内删除。若因私自散布造成法律问题，本组概不负责。如果喜欢本作品，请购买并支持正版！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.15,0:02:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是12月25日
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.91,0:02:50.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是结业典礼的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.21,0:02:54.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说昨天真是吓死了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.38,0:02:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.43,0:02:56.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贞子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.84,0:02:59.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然来参加二次聚会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.97,0:03:07.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田她们把麦克风交给她后唱了一首
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.29,0:03:10.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就立刻回家了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.12,0:03:16.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说那时候她好像是和风早一起来的 是错觉么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.73,0:03:18.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也觉得是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.03,0:03:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就算是风早也不至于...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.47,0:03:23.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真是笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.52,0:03:27.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我叫爽子来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.12,0:21:04.42,Warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,banner;28;0;60,人员表 翻译 瑶瑶 老虎 校译 时间 阿虚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.20,0:03:32.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为风早昨天玩游戏输给我了 才让他等爽子的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.70,0:03:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子也不知道二次聚会的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.70,0:03:42.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不到时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.99,0:03:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这之后还有情人节等等有趣的节日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.91,0:03:50.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能让你们去破坏别人的好事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.23,0:03:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.53,0:03:58.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是比起这个爽子更是个问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.66,0:04:03.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄的不好的话 会说出风早的名誉什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.57,0:04:04.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.86,0:04:05.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.52,0:04:07.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.02,0:04:11.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 打招呼的时候有人回应了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.14,0:04:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 风早
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.29,0:04:19.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天很早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.95,0:04:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都很早
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.73,0:04:23.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪天早了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.75,0:04:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是腹带
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.38,0:04:34.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是一针针
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.78,0:04:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着对父亲的感激之情编织的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.06,0:04:40.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 不是给我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.00,0:04:46.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微出了点差错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.07,0:04:49.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和准备给你的礼物弄错了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.36,0:04:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 如果可以的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.00,0:04:57.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请风早同学的父亲呀母亲呀或者是爷爷使用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.77,0:04:59.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我收下也没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.75,0:05:05.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.99,0:05:11.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好温柔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.86,0:05:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明自己根本不会用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.31,0:05:16.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是很开心的收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.15,0:05:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 就算帽子的话也不会戴的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.20,0:05:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对风早来说 不管两者都没差别吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.34,0:05:27.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.34,0:05:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.45,0:05:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然对我来说不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.35,0:05:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所包含的感情也不同
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.12,0:05:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天雪下的真是大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.51,0:05:43.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领带
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.81,0:05:46.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天是结业典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.03,0:05:50.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越耀眼了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.23,0:05:54.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.09,0:05:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 小千
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.09,0:05:58.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 阿爽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.89,0:05:59.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.07,0:06:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 矢野 风早
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.33,0:06:04.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天这么冷 你还真是精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.41,0:06:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 今天是结业典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.68,0:06:11.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就是寒假了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.64,0:06:15.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会变得稍微有点寂寞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.98,0:06:22.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.35,0:06:25.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.79,0:06:27.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别堵在门口不动快进去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.29,0:06:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是善啊 是班主任 好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.28,0:06:35.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 事出突然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.79,0:06:39.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定要继承妻子老家的造酒屋了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.65,0:06:42.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此今天是最后一天做大家的班主任了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.71,0:06:45.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.14,0:06:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体呢 不是不好么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.25,0:06:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 身体好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.02,0:06:51.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是遭到不幸了么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.15,0:06:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 酒屋那里工作已上轨道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.86,0:06:57.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妻子老家那边也家族圆满团圆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.31,0:07:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反了么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.92,0:07:03.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒井老师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.01,0:07:06.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告别会呢 开告别会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.53,0:07:10.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们 但是今天一定要回去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.25,0:07:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和大家一起度过的日子我绝不会忘记的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.60,0:07:15.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿善...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.05,0:07:21.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么给本大爷开个新班主任崇拜会也可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.67,0:07:28.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 总之要开结业典礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.89,0:07:30.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家去走廊排队
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.38,0:07:33.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别出列哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.81,0:07:39.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人激动的第二学期
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.08,0:07:54.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使做鬼脸也很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.12,0:07:57.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了很多事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.31,0:08:01.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就是寒假了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.44,0:08:03.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要玩的太过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.36,0:08:05.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请务必小心各种事故
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.14,0:08:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健健康康的迎接新的一年
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.85,0:08:14.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的发生了很多的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.62,0:08:46.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然也有痛苦的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.48,0:08:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是开心的事多了好多好多倍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.25,0:09:05.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这是大家给老师写的联名卡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:07.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑 黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.03,0:09:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 这玩意儿是避邪的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.92,0:09:13.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起立
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.52,0:09:16.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然外表看上去没有变化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.33,0:09:18.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.35,0:09:25.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也考虑了 经历了很多新的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.22,0:09:28.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 明天就是寒假了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.41,0:09:32.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找地方吃点什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.43,0:09:33.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.92,0:09:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.91,0:09:37.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.37,0:09:40.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去卡拉OK吧 卡拉OK
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.61,0:09:41.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是昨天去过了么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.92,0:09:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去的话 第三学期前就见不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.68,0:09:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年多谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.27,0:10:02.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏你 过的很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.17,0:10:07.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早 走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.63,0:10:13.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了 要简短的说下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.69,0:10:14.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.87,0:10:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,bye bye
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.93,0:10:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你过个好年
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.59,0:10:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年再见
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.90,0:10:47.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不错啊 爽子爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.47,0:10:49.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邮箱地址设置了么 邮箱地址
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.70,0:10:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 说明书还没完全看完
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.88,0:10:55.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算全部看遍么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.34,0:10:56.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用看也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.59,0:10:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你弄 给我下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.97,0:11:01.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.21,0:11:03.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邮箱名用什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.59,0:11:04.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.02,0:11:07.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字长点的话 垃圾邮件会少些
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.22,0:11:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如名字呀 生日之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.39,0:11:13.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.82,0:11:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}(爽子.不是.贞子.1231@xx)
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.93,0:11:21.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好厉害 还有解除误会的功能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.56,0:11:25.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 你生日是除夕那天么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.75,0:11:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.80,0:11:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 绫音 那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.24,0:11:42.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话寒假里我们也能见面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.94,0:11:44.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如空闲的日子里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.70,0:11:52.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常~~~~~闲的日子什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.66,0:11:56.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说如果方便的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.59,0:11:59.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个笨蛋啊 当然是可以的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.00,0:12:03.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在还说这样的话 真是吓了一跳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.61,0:12:06.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联络也变方便了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.73,0:12:15.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用等到第三学期了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.60,0:12:22.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除夕那天啊 我一直都是和龙一起去神社的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.44,0:12:25.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年矢野和爽子要不要一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.01,0:12:28.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.52,0:12:32.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除夕那天能见到大家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.60,0:12:33.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.22,0:12:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先和家里确认下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.68,0:12:42.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.50,0:12:47.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊拉 是和小千 绫音一起吗 可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.11,0:12:50.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等爸爸回来了 你和他说一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.65,0:12:52.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也觉得自己昨天做错事了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.70,0:12:54.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会拒绝的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.95,0:12:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.10,0:13:02.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来 昨天她是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.20,0:13:08.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以见面了 在除夕那天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.40,0:13:13.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成16岁的日子 可以和大家在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.38,0:13:18.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽子知道风早的电话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.09,0:13:22.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 其实昨天见到的时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.06,0:13:25.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经和他联络过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.94,0:13:27.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 也没有什么事情...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.02,0:13:30.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就有事情了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.47,0:13:34.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前的状况是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.06,0:13:39.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去参拜神社的人只有小千 龙 爽子和我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.54,0:13:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不介意的话那就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.86,0:13:47.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想见风早的话 那就自己去邀请他吧 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.99,0:13:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邀请!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.06,0:13:53.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在不立刻联系他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.68,0:13:56.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风早肯定很快就会有预定了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.53,0:13:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不用勉强
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.86,0:14:02.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想见他的话 明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.10,0:14:07.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在不联系他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.86,0:14:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次见面就是第三学期了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.62,0:14:19.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不知道他的邮件地址 所以就打电话...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.42,0:14:23.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是黑沼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.48,0:14:26.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是黑沼...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.10,0:14:30.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去参拜神社的除夕...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.92,0:14:32.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.77,0:14:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我们也跟着紧张了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.25,0:14:43.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能见到 那就太幸运了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.17,0:14:48.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且会非常开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.39,0:14:58.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.95,0:15:09.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.18,0:15:12.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我是黑沼...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.55,0:15:22.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问除夕那天要不要一起去参拜神社
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.16,0:15:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千 绫音 真田同学也一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.15,0:15:28.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很闲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.48,0:15:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 是如果你也有空的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.21,0:15:32.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.16,0:15:36.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田 矢野 龙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.20,0:15:38.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有黑沼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.84,0:15:40.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会妨碍大家的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.55,0:15:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去 我很期待那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.84,0:15:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他很期待
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.35,0:15:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那不是很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.00,0:15:55.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.75,0:15:58.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能见到他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.55,0:16:02.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是在生日那天
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.93,0:16:07.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能见到他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.66,0:16:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接来下...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.84,0:16:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.86,0:16:17.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像做梦一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.36,0:16:25.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时光流转
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.28,0:16:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了12月31日 除夕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.85,0:16:33.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 不用收拾了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.37,0:16:37.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千和绫音马上就会过来接你了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.88,0:16:41.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 不能让朋友们等太久
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.76,0:16:43.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.43,0:16:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会穿上妈妈送的披肩的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.14,0:16:51.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 爽子要和朋友一起去参拜神社了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.85,0:16:56.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千和绫音是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.88,0:17:01.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真田同学和风早同学也是我的朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.21,0:17:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是风早同学...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.41,0:17:10.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了哦 晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.78,0:17:13.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.88,0:17:15.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.95,0:17:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.48,0:17:19.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就去穿外套
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.43,0:17:22.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我们可以先进来下吗 去爽子的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.53,0:17:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进请进
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.36,0:17:28.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.59,0:17:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.37,0:17:35.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不要乱动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.65,0:17:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.93,0:17:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 这么淡的妆不会被察觉的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.73,0:17:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 向下看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.84,0:17:46.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.13,0:17:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要眨眼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.23,0:17:55.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见到胡桃的时候 不是想过要变得可爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.84,0:18:00.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么想要变可爱 自己好好想想
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.76,0:18:03.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 完成
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.29,0:18:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.73,0:18:07.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是矢野和我送给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.62,0:18:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐 爽子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.11,0:18:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好可爱 好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.40,0:18:22.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是我们的杰作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.99,0:18:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.49,0:18:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发夹也很合适
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.50,0:18:28.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.17,0:18:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,stop 不要哭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.84,0:18:31.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍住 绝对要忍住
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.30,0:18:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能浪费两个人的心血
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.59,0:18:40.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化妆之后 更添魄力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.08,0:18:43.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.07,0:18:46.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.06,0:18:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常 非常的幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.91,0:18:54.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年与你们相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.10,0:18:58.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了很多很多开心的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.16,0:19:01.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.89,0:19:05.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离约好的地点也已经很近了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.33,0:19:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们消失吧 小千
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.46,0:19:07.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的是 矢野
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.29,0:19:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.49,0:19:11.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就先闪了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.95,0:19:16.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和风早两个人玩得开心的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.91,0:19:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.71,0:19:20.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用介意我们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.32,0:19:23.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙也不会过去的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.38,0:19:24.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.15,0:19:26.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等下要和我们报告哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.60,0:19:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕什么啊 明明是你自己邀请他的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.54,0:20:07.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让我和他相见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.47,0:20:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小千和绫音才会努力的把我打扮的可爱一点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.80,0:20:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙还没来 吉田和矢野呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.73,0:20:21.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.20,0:20:26.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真田同学也不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.91,0:20:30.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他失望了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.18,0:20:36.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很为难吗 会不会不去了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.55,0:20:47.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.68,0:21:00.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12月31日
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.75,0:21:12.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离新年还有30分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:25.92,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飞满了纸飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いかない　それが答えてなんだって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:36.24,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要走 那就是回答
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,シャボン玉　飛ばそう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.49,0:21:39.65,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡泡 飘飘浮浮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空まではきっと届かない　うちに壊れてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:47.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还未到达天空就破灭消散而去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま誰知りたいの永遠じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:53.46,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我们想要的永远
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままずっと　いていたいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.72,0:22:01.12,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管想要永远留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その空一杯の紙飛行機　暗いになって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:12.39,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空中飞满了纸飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edj,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひとつだけ見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.20,0:22:21.93,edc,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只找寻到了属于我的唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.18,0:22:34.19,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(693,364)}第24话 生日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.88,0:22:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,编织在一起的语言
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.61,0:22:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在雪停的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.56,0:22:34.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一话 生日

